不  我知道  我忘记了
No, I know, I forgot.
我昨晚应该做的
I should have done it last night.
周日来不及做
I didn't finish Sunday.
回去已经太晚
I didn't get back till late.
我到店里就做
I'll sort it out as soon as I get in.
我答应你  马上做
I promise you, as soon as I get it.
不  我保证
No, I promise you, mate.
好
Okay.
好  我快到了
All right, I'm literally around the corner now.
你在哪里？
Where are you?
转角  马上到
Around the corner, give me two seconds.
快点
Hurry up. Hurry up.
好  再见
All right, ta'ra, ta'ra, ta'ra.
嗨  我是凯莉
Hi, you've reached Kelly.
请留言
Leave me a message.
我会尽快回覆
I'll get back to you as soon as I can.
再见
Bye.
凯莉  抱歉我没做
Oh, Kelly I'm real sorry I missed it.
最近杂事太多
I've just had so much shit on.
懂我的意思吗？
Do you know what I mean?
我累翻了
I'm... I'm devastated,
真的真的很抱歉
and I'm really, really, really sorry.
不敢相信啊
I can't fucking believe it.
整个一团乱
I, me head was all over the place.
懂我的意思吗？靠
You know what I mean? Ah, fuck.
告诉他我很抱歉
Just tell him I'm so sorry,
我会在他睡前打给他  好吗？
and I'll, I'll phone him before he goes to bed, yeah?
一定要跟他说
But please, please tell him I'm
我真的很抱歉
really, really, really fucking sorry.
我…太多事情了
I don't, I... I've... I've... I've just got so much going on.
懂我的意思吗？
Do you know what I mean?
这两个月工作压力很大
I've been living out of a suitcase for the past two fucking months.
昨晚才搬完家
Only moved in last night.
你知道的  不是…
So, you know, it's not...
我知道我不对  告诉他
I know it's my fault, but just tell him
我会在他睡前打给他
I'll tell him I'll phone him before he goes to bed.
好吗？好
Okay? All right.
对不起  再见
Sorry. Ta'ra, bye.
- '早安'  主厨  - 真合理
- Morning, chef. - Fair enough.
- 主厨要咖啡吗？  - 双份  比尔
- Chef's coffee chef? - Yeah. Double, bill.
- 不好意思  琼斯先生？  - 是？
- Sorry, Mr. Jones? - Yeah?
我是艾伦·洛夫乔伊  环境卫生…
I'm Alan lovejoy, I'm the environmental health...
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
你没事吧？
Are you okay to crack on?
没事  给我几分钟？
Yeah. Just give me a couple of minutes. Yeah?
- 好  - 马上来
- All right. - I'll be right back.
你慢慢来
As soon as you're ready, please.
- 让我换衣服  - 谢谢
- Let me get changed. - Thank you.
好  卡莉  我们来收尾？
All right, Carly, should we just finish up?
一边巡一边等他
We can recap a couple of things while we're waiting for him.
- 好  - 那个没了
- Okay. - That one's off.
你说你叫陶比？
You've already said Toby?
- 东尼  - 东尼
- Tony. - Tony.
开店前要处理好吧？
We're going to get this in order before we open, yeah?
不能等到明天
Of course. Not tomorrow?
好  别让安迪看到
Okay, don't let Andy see you.
是
Yeah.
在安迪来之前处理完
Clean this shit up before Andy gets here.
- 不好意思  你刚刚…  - 动作快
- Sorry did you just- - no, just do it.
在备餐水槽洗手？
Just wash your hands in the food preparation sink?
- 是  - 是
- Yes. - Yeah.
知道洗手
You're aware we wash our hands in the,
要去洗手台吗？
in the hand washing sink over there?
- 我…  - 她新来的
- No, I uh... - She's new.
- 你什么名字？  - 卡蜜儿
- What's your name? - Camille.
卡蜜儿
Camille.
做多久了  卡蜜儿？
How long have you been here, Camille?
- 大概一周  - 好
- A week or so. - Okay.
上过餐饮卫生课吗？
Have you been on any food hygiene courses,
有证照吗？
accreditation at all?
有啦  二级证照
Yeah. No. She's got a level two.
她有二级？好
She's got a level two? Okay.
我离开之前拿给我看
Well, if you could show me that before I leave?
- 是  - 很好
- Yeah. Absolutely. - That would be brilliant.
卡蜜儿  会洗手很好
Camille, I'm glad you're washing your hands,
但不要在备餐水槽好吗？
just not where we prepare food. Okay?
我相信你懂的
I'm sure you knew that though.
- 尽量…  - 好  我知道
- Just... - Okay. I know. I know.
好的  接下来冰箱
All right, so we set them fridges,
温度是...
and that is...
刚好符合标准
That's just about regulation.
也就是？
Which of course is?
- ８度  - ８度
- Eight degrees. - Eight degrees.
但可以更好  就像厨房各部位
But ideally, like the ones around there
我喜欢低一点
I prefer it to be a bit lower
５度更理想
in the region of five would be ideal.
但规定是８度？
But eight degrees is regulation?
- 规定是８度  - 所以符合规定？
- Eight degrees is regulation. - So we meet regulation?
- 确实符合规定  - 很好
- You do meet regulation. - Great.
不  我要说的是
But no, no, but what I'm saying is
如果冰箱很满
if you packed that fridge anymore, the circulation
冷藏循环变差
of the air is not gonna be able to get around
食材容易坏掉
and you're gonna have to waste a load more food.
懂吗？因为它会超过８度
Okay? Because it's going to go above eight degrees.
疏忽容易犯错  卡莉
So always err on the side of caution, Carly.
就像路易斯先生说的  另一位稽查
Like Mr. Lewis said, the other inspector
不要因小失大
don't risk it for a biscuit.
这就是我们宣导的
That's what we try and say.
不好意思  你好？
Sorry. Hello? Hello?
没什么…
All right, it's all right...
先把刀放下？
Do you want to put the knife down a second?
- 不好意思  - 谢谢
- Yes, sorry. - Thank you.
简单说一下
Let's have a quick word,
说你负责什么
just talk me through what you're doing.
好  我们为今晚准备鸭肉
Well, we're prepping duck for this evening.
准备鸭肉
Prepping duck.
好  怎样做？
Okay, and how would you do that?
做我正在做的
Well, do what I'm doing now,
先煎过  然后放烤箱
and then we pan fry it and put it in the oven.
鸭肉煮到几度？
At what temperature would you cook the duck to?
- 63度  - 63
- 63 degrees. - 63.
怎么检查？
And you check that how?
- 用探针  - 用探针
- With a probe. - With a probe.
- 固定这样做吗？  - 每餐都是
- And you do that regularly? - Every meal.
- 都会检查  - 对
- And you keep checks. - Yep.
很棒  谢谢
Lovely. Thank you.
壁砖  你说结构损坏？
The tiles, you said the structural damage?
对  厂商明天来修
Yeah, contractors coming tomorrow.
明天  修好拍照
Coming tomorrow, and as soon as you take a picture of that
可以发电邮给我
you can actually email that to me.
他一直抓胡子  你知道吗？
Keeps itching his beard, do you know that?
他会洗手  没事
It's fine he washes his hands. It's fine.
好吧  保持手洗干净
Okay. Well, as long as he does regularly.
谢谢
Thank you.
尽快发电邮给我
Yeah, you could email me that as soon as you've got-
- 是  - 你…
- yeah. Yeah. - Would you?
艾蜜莉？
Emily? Emily?
我们的甜点主厨  艾蜜莉
This is our head of pastry, Emily
这位是甜点师杰米
and this is our commie pastry chef, Jamie.
杰米  幸会  其实…
Jamie, nice to meet you. We actually have-
我认得你
- I was going to say, I recognize your face.
之前见过  在霍斯顿  你的面包店
We have met before. Your bakery in hoxton.
- 胖胖卷  - 胖胖卷！
- Rolly pollies. - Rolly pollies!
- 对  你记得  - 没错
- Yes, you remember. - Yes, absolutely.
你的香蕉蛋糕有那个…
Your banana, your banana cake had this-
- 谢谢  - 黑巧克力
- thank you very much. - Dark chocolate.
- 对  - 很棒吧？
- Yes. - It's beautiful isn't it?
- 你吃过  杰米？  - 超爱吃
- Have you tried it, Jamie? - Oh, I love it.
- 他吃过好几次  - 极品
- He's had it a few times. - Out of this world.
- 你好吗？  - 还不错  谢谢
- How are you? - I'm not too bad thank you.
- 不错？  - 对
- You good? - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- 你看起来很好  - 过来看一下
- You look really, really well. - Come now. No, now please.
还不错啦  不意外…
No not too bad I'm not surprised-
- 艾蜜莉  - 是？
- Emily. Emily. - Yes, darling?
- 可以吗？  - 可以  没事
- You all right? - Yeah, we're fine.
- 你掌厨
I'm not surprised this is all an order
难怪很有条理  - 感恩
- with you working here. - Bless you.
我巡了大概半小时
I've been round about half hour ago
- 该说的都说了  - 还好吗？
- and it's all tipped off. - All good?
杰米  你做多久了？
Jamie. Jamie, how long have you been there?
大概三周
About three weeks.
抱歉  还要稽查多久？
Excuse me mate, how long is this gonna take?
该多久就多久
Well, it will take as long as it takes.
感谢关照  可是快开店了
And I appreciate that, but we've got to open up,
我知道
well, I know that.
其实已经验完了  我在等你
We are actually about done, I'm waiting for you.
我们简短说一下？
Can we just have a quick word?
到前面说  可以吗？
All right if we go out there?
好  当然
Yeah, course, yeah.
- 我们单独说  - 艾蜜莉
Just you and me. All right. Emily.
好  很高兴见到你
Its lovely, lovely to see you.
- 很好  - 圣诞快乐
- It was really love- - have a lovely Christmas.
你也是  杰米  很高兴认识你
And yourself. Jamie. Good to meet you.
好  不耽误你
Okay. I don't want to keep you any longer than we have to.
请坐  谢谢
Just take a seat. Thank you.
好
Okay.
来看一下哪些需要处理
So let's see what we're dealing with here.
- 好  - 好
- Okay. - All right.
不好意思
Sorry.
首先  你要知道这些重点
Primarily, that's all the information you need to know.
我不会逐一说明
I'm not going to go through with you all today,
因为整体有点落后了
because we're running a bit behind.
都在这里  卡莉知道
But it's all there, Carly knows it all.
这是你的总评
And, that's your sticker.
五星降到三星
You've gone down from a five to a three.
好吗？我说明一下
All right? I'm going to tell you why.
- 降很多  对吧?  - 对
- That's a big drop, init? - It is.
主要是因为你的备查资料
It's primarily because of your... your documentation.
还有记录资料
Okay? And your record keeping.
- 大致如此  - 洗手台？
- And it's quite frankly- - wash basin?
洗手台  法国人
Wash basin. It's the French...
- 卡蜜儿  法国女生  - 是？
- Camille? French lady? - Yeah?
她在备餐水槽洗手
She's washing her hands in the food preparation sink,
但这不是重点
but that's not the main thing I'm concerned about.
我关心的重点是…
The main thing I'm concerned about, is that, could I...
麻烦注意听
Could I have your attention?
我关心的重点是这个
The main thing I'm concerned about is this, okay.
你做得不够好
You've got big gaps here.
差很多  我们应该每天做确实
Massive gaps, where we should be filling in daily.
监控冰箱温度
Taking... taking... Taking fridge temperatures.
我相信他们有在做
I'm assured they're done every day.
- 不过…  - 生蚝怎么了？
- But if we come... - What's with the oysters?
生蚝  备料区乱七八糟
The oysters over there, his sections a mess.
我刚才经过看到
Okay. I just walked passed him
他没有处理干净
and he's still not cleaned it up.
他的手套  备料时没戴手套
It' his gloves, he's without gloves on cross-contamination
整个不行  不用我讲
the lot, I don't need to tell you that.
那把刀要换
Okay. You'll need to replace that knife.
对我来说很明显不够好
So what is obvious to me is there's lots of gaps
两个月前还勉强合格
up until two months ago is filled in quite regularly.
现在差很多
Now we've got gaps.
注意需要补足的
Look at where it should be filled in.
检查项目一览表
And the opening and closing checks,
该监督的人
someone who's meant to do them.
- 对  就是我  - 你亲自监督
- Yeah. That's me. - Yourself. Yourself.
好的  如果你忙不过来
Okay. Well, if you're not able to do it
就要找人做
someone should come in,
安排负责人
and you should have that in place for someone to do it.
这些都很基本  琼斯先生
These are basic things, Mr. Jones,
会扣分的
and it's going to bring your score down.
老问题  麻烦你注意听
It keeps, can I have your attention?
只要做好这些  我就不会来了
As soon as we get this done I can leave.
早点讲完
And the sooner we get this done,
早点解脱
the sooner we can move on
让你回到你的岗位
and get you back up to where you should be.
之前是五星
Before this, which was a five.
但你管理的信心下降了
But your confidence in management has gone right down,
是主要原因
because of this. All right?
应该要有'傻瓜指引'
This should be like an idiot's guide.
遇到你休假  卡莉休假
So if you're off, if Carly's off.
各种情况  任何人都能依照指引
For some reason, anyone could pick this up
继续让餐厅安全的、有效的营运
and can make this place run smoothly safely, effectively.
我知道这些东西很烦
I know it's a pain in the arse,
但这是有必要的烦
but it's a necessary pain in the arse.
好  今天到这里
Okay. So let's leave it there.
好
Okay.
你可以申诉
So, you can appeal.
我不建议那样做
I wouldn't advise that.
你的情况  申诉只会浪费时间
I'd say it'd be a waste of the time in your case,
最下面有我的电邮
but the bottom here is my email.
好吗？  a.lovejoy
Okay? A. Lovejoy.
三个月后找我复查
Three months' time, you get in contact with me
回到五星
and we'll get you back up to a five,
前提是符合规定  好吗？
if you follow this criteria, all right?
你要把它整顿好
But you're going to need to get this in order.
最后一件事
Oh, one last thing.
厨房不准放玻璃杯  你知道的
No glass in the kitchen, but you knew that.
好的  圣诞快乐
All right? Have a good Christmas.
祝你顺利
All the best.
贝丝  谈一下？
Beth, Beth can I have a quick word?
- 是  好的
Yes, yes, of course.
- 检查怎么样？
How was it?
艾蜜莉！杰米！
Emily. Jamie.
- 是
Yeah. Yes.
看一下
Have a look at that.
上面写什么？
What's that say?
上面写三星
Oh dear, it says a three.
- 你说什么？  - 上面写三星
- Sorry? - It says a three.
三星  很严重欸
Three, that's fucking massive.
几乎腰斩  对吧？
That's, I mean that's a jump and a half, init?
原本是五星  现在三星
We were a five and now we're a three.
他来这里抓问题
What he comes down, has a nose about
就是这样  我们三星了？
and that's it, we're a three?
开什么玩笑？
It's a fucking joke. Init?
你怎样洗手  小姐？
How do wash your hands, love?
- 我知道  - 怎样洗？
- I know. - Sorry what?
在水槽
In the sink.
- 在水槽  哪个水槽？  - 好了啦  安迪
- In the sink. Which sink? - All right, Andy.
- 那个  - 哪个水槽？
- Back there. - Which sink?
- 卡莉  - 没有啦  她…
- Hang on Carly. - No, no, no she's been...
卡莉  等一下
Carly, wait a minute, love.
卡莉  这很基本欸  中学毕业…
Carly, Carly this is fucking basic gcse fucking-
对  她到职第一周  我该负责
- yeah, and it's her first week, so it's my responsibility.
但她不是第一周进厨房
It's not her first week in any fucking kitchen though,
对吧？
is it?
你在厨房做过吧？
You've worked in kitchens before haven't ya?
- 是  - 是  所以雇用你
- Yes. - Yeah, that's why you're here.
你在厨房做过  是吧？
You've worked in kitchens before, yeah?
- 是  - 是什么？
- Yes. - Yes what?
- 是  主厨  - 是  主厨
- Yes chef. - Yes chef.
- 那水槽干嘛用的  小朋友？  - 备餐
- So what's that sink for, kid? - Food.
- 干嘛用？  - 备餐
- For what? - Food.
你在那个水槽干嘛？
What do you not do in that sink?
- 洗手  - 洗什么？
- Wash your hands. - Wash your what?
- 手  - 洗手  好
- Hands. - Wash your hands. Yeah.
搞什么东西
Fucking gobshite here.
你搞错水槽
You, using the wrong fucking sink,
你  废物  你做什么？
and you, soft ass, what are you playing at?
什么意思  主厨？
What do you mean, chef?
什么意思  什么意思？
What do we mean, what do I mean?
你负责什么啦？
What the fuck are you doing?
我不就水产类助手吗
I'm not, I'm not supposed to be on a section chef.
东尼  你做多久了  小子？
Tony, how long have you worked here, lad?
我做了  不对  做兴趣的…
I've been here, no, but it's hobbs...
- 东尼
Tony.
东尼  你做多久了  小子？
Tony, how long have you worked here, son?
- 一年  - 一年
- A year. - A year.
他说你没戴手套啦
He's saying you've got no fucking gloves on.
处理生蚝交叉污染
Cross contamination with the oysters.
- 知道了  主厨  对不起  - 戴手套啦
- I got, chef, sorry. - Put your fucking gloves on.
- 对不起  - 戴手套  小子
- Sorry. - Put your gloves on, son.
你最好搞清楚  小子
Now, listen, Tony, you buck your fucking ideas up, lad,
外面一百万个年轻人
cause there's a million kids out there who would die
抢着要做你的工作
for this fucking opportunity that you've been given.
是  主厨  谢谢主厨
Yes, chef. Thank you, chef
尊重一下  尊重你的工作啦
show some fucking respect. Respects your fucking self.
认真一点啦
Pull your fucking socks up.
- 对不起  主厨  - 好
- Sorry chef. - Yes.
好  你们每个人做好该做的
Right, look, every single one of yous, that goes for all yous.
清清楚楚
Right across the board.
负责做好该做的
Sort your own fucking sections out.
- 好吗？  - 好  主厨
- Yeah? - Yes, chef.
好  我们可以的
All right, we're going to get this
回到五星
back up to a fucking five.
- 好吗？  - 好  厨师
- Yeah? - Yes, chef.
好  说一下？
Okay. All right, where are we?
我们尽量准备了
Right? We've called in what we could,
某些食材不太够
but we're still a bit tight on some items.
还是可以出一份很好的菜单
But I think we've still got a good menu.
生蚝、鲑鱼、肝都很好
So we are fine on the oysters, the salmon, the liver.
我们的汤有点少
We're a bit low on the soup.
牛肉完全用光了
We couldn't get beef anywhere.
我很抱歉
Okay look, I'm sorry about that.
没事没事
It's all right. It's all right.
- 不做牛肉  - 要做  我再打给他
- The beefs off. - No, I'll phone him in a bit.
- 我晚点去找史密斯  - 来不及
- I'll get on smiths in a bit. - It's too late.
没关系  我们有鲭鱼
It's fine. We've got mackerel.
有鸭肉炖饭
We've got duck brill Risotto.
羊肉的量刚刚好？
Now, we've got just about enough lamb?
羊肉不够
No, we haven't got enough lamb.
量应该还够
We've got enough. We've got enough.
我说了很抱歉
Yeah, I've said I'm sorry, lad.
- 你还想怎样？  - 不是我的问题
- What's your fucking problem? - What's my problem?
安迪  每次都这样
Andy, it's time and time a-fucking-gain.
执行的人不是你
You're not doing the orders, man.
- 费里曼  - 我没办法做事
- Freeman, Freeman. - I can't do my work.
我犯错了  昨晚没准备  好吗？
I made a mistake. I didn't do them last night, did I?
对不起  我有道歉吧？
I'm sorry. I apologize. Have I said sorry?
我有道歉吧？
Have I said sorry?
反正完了  没差
We've blagged it, it's fine.
- 我有道歉吧？  - 我们今晚有菜单
- I've said sorry, haven't I? - We've got a menu for tonight.
我有道歉  可以了吧？
Okay, I've said sorry. Van we leave it?
争这个也没用  对吧？
Look, there's no use crying about it, is there?
我们继续？
Can we just get on with it?
只要继续做
We've just got to get on with it.
有很好的菜单
We've go a good menu.
大家合作  会没事的
We'll pull together, we'll be fine.
- 好吗？  - 好  二厨
- Yes? - Yes, chef.
同意吗？
No, come on. Are you with me?
- 是  二厨  - 谢谢
- Yes, chef! - Thank you.
继续讲你的
Can we just get on with it?
- 好  - 好的
- Yes. - Okay. Yeah.
- 认真点  费里曼  - 好啦
- Watch it, Freeman. - Okay. All right.
处理好  可以吗？
Let's sort it out. You okay?
- 好  没事  - 确定？
- Yes, no we're all good. - Yeah, you sure?
- 对  - 好
- Yeah. - Okay.
好  另一件事
Okay, now the other thing,
我们没有比目鱼
we haven't got any turbot.
什么意思？
What you mean?
他扔掉了
He threw it away.
什么叫'他扔掉了'？
What do you mean he threw it, fucking hell?
打扰一下
What? Excuse me.
你为什么扔掉？
Why'd you let him throw it away?
其实…
It wasn't...
你知道这东西很贵吗？
Do you know how fucking expensive this stuff is?
其实…
It wasn't...
你怎么让他扔了  卡莉？
Why'd you let him throw it away, Carly?
没标记
It wasn't labeled.
什么叫'没标记'？
What do you mean it wasn't labeled?
怎么会没标记啦？
Why wasn't it fucking labeled?
安迪  你昨晚该准备的
Andy, you prepped it last night.
好
All right.
- 好  - 没事
- All right. - It's all right.
- 对不起  - 没关系
- All right, I'm sorry. - It's all right.
我太忙了  对不起  我道歉
I've got fucking loads going on, I'm sorry, I apologize.
没关系
It's fine. It's fine.
来  我们把它处理好
Come on look, we need to crack on.
我会处理  马上处理好
I'll get on that as well, sort that one out in a minute.
没关系  来吧
It's all right. Come on. Come on.
你处理一下
You take five minutes yeah.
好  我去做
All right, I'll go and do the orders.
- 好的  - 我现在去叫货
- Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. - I'll go make the orders now.
大家动起来
Come on, everybody. Let's move our arses.
是  二厨
Yes, chef.
换档冲起来
Yeah. Let's shift into gear now.
- 抱歉  - 没关系
- I'm sorry. - It's all right.
对不起  我居然忘了
No, I'm sorry, can't believe I forgot.
你没事吧？有睡觉吗？
You're all right? Yeah? Have you slept?
主厨？
Chef?
有睡一点
Yeah a little bit. A little bit.
好  下次记得要通知我
Okay, but look next time, just make sure you call me.
- 主厨！  - 如果你通知我…
- Chef. - If you call me I...
我知道啦
Okay, I know. I know. All right.
刚才送他出去
I've just seen him on the way out.
五星降到三星？
We went from a five to a three star?
- 我知道  对  - 为什么？
- I know, yeah. - Why?
厨房没事  食材没事
The kitchen's fine. The food's fine and all that.
- 到底为什么？  - 表单而已
- So why? - It's the paperwork.
- 为什么表单没做  - 我没把表单做完整
- Why isn't the paperwork done? - I'm behind on the paperwork.
为什么？
Why?
反正我没监督好啦
It's just fucking... I haven't managed it properly.
- 懂吗？  - 丢脸
- Do you know what I mean? - That's fucking embarrassing.
哪里丢脸？我会补好
What do you mean it's embarrassing? I'll get on it.
- 处理好  - 只有三个月
- Sort it out. - It's only for three months.
十分钟后开店
We open in 10 minutes.
安迪  什么事？
Andy, what was that all about?
她在讲降到三星
She's going on about us being a three.
- 我会处理好  - 好
- I'll sort it. I'll fix it. - Okay, all right.
我去叫货
I'll make the orders now.
等一下  安迪  你有讲吗？
Wait look, look, look, Andy, have you managed
跟和她谈加薪？
to talk to her about a wage increase?
我有讲
Yeah. Yeah, I did.
昨晚跟她讲了
I had a chat with her last night.
- 然后？  - 她会处理
- Yeah, and? - She's gonna get on to it.
什么叫'会处理'？
What do you mean she's gonna get on to it?
她有在做
I mean, she's got it sorted.
我说了这件事今晚要有答案
I told you that job needs an answer tonight.
我答应你
No, I promise you.
安迪  我今晚找她谈
Andy, I need to tell him tonight.
- 卡莉  我答应你  - 我今晚找她谈
- Carly, I promise you. - I need to tell him tonight.
今晚会处理好  我答应你
I'll have it sorted by tonight. I promise you.
你保证？
You promise?
是啊  我让你失望过吗？
Yeah, have I ever let you down?
- 好吧  - 从来没有吧
- Okay. Yep. - I've never, yeah, okay.
你还好吗？我很抱歉
And you're okay? I'm sorry about that.
是我的错
Yes, it was my fault.
不  是我的错  不应该吼你
No it was my fault, I shouldn't have shouted at you.
- 没关系  - 好
- It's okay. - Okay.
你在做什么  废物？
What are you doing, soft lad?
给我
Give us here.
这不是我该做的  厨师
It's not my section, chef.
我知道不是
I know it's not your section now,
但加减帮忙嘛
but were all chipping in aren't we?
这样  注意看
Give it here. Watch. Yeah.
这样就对了
Just get it right, yeah?
稍微转一下  很顺
Twist it nice and gentle,
放在下面  类似骑重机
get it underneath, like a motorbike, yeah?
温柔一点
And just caress it through.
温柔是吧
Caress it yeah?
大家  流程简报
Guys, staff briefing now.
贝丝  我们在赶工
Beth, we've got to make this quick.
- 什么？  - 然后撬开
- What? - And then pop it.
进度落后了在赶工
We're really behind. We've got to make this quick.
来吧
Come on.
大家来唷
Come on, everybody.
安迪  别接电话
Andy, don't pick the phone up!
- 不要接电话  - 你好
- Don't pick the phone up. - Hello.
安迪  流程简报
Andy, staff briefing now.
好  没有
Okay. Yeah. Yeah. No, no.
我很抱歉  我有留言
I'm really sorry love, yeah. I left you a message.
- 安迪  挂掉  - 对  我在开会
- Andy, now phone down. - Yeah, I'm just in a meeting.
有时间就回你
I'll phone you back as soon as I get a chance.
好  再见
Yeah, alright bye.
罗苹在哪？
Come on, where's Robin?
- 她在试镜  - 她在哪？
- She's at an audition. - She where?
她在路上
She's on her way, she's on her way.
抱歉  又来了
No, sorry that was another day.
- 她在路上  - 她会来的
- She's on her way. - She's got time.
- 杰克呢？  - 杰克迟到
- And where's, where's Jake? - Jake is late.
他总是迟到
He's always late by the way.
要处理一下
You have to do something about it.
疯狂周五  会很忙  这样也好
Okay. Mad Friday, it's going to be busy, which is good.
有追加订位
And we've picked some more covers up today.
预计一百桌
So we're looking at about hundred.
所以收拾要快  但是
So we've got to turn the tables over, but obviously
不能让客人觉得急忙
not make people feel rushed, yeah?
这个可以
Good, which we can do.
今晚有新人求婚
We've got a proposal in tonight.
他们坐13桌
They're gonna be sat on table 13.
没错  向王室一样招待他们
So, yeah, treat them like royalty,
还有名厨亚历山大·斯凯
and celebrity chef in Alexander Skye.
他坐外场最前面
He's gonna be sat in the front.
亚历史塔·斯凯
Alistair, alistair Skye.
对  就是他
Yeah, yeah him.
他坐最前面
He's gonna be sat at the front.
他桌上要有庄园的  比利？
Bottle of chateau on his table Billy, yeah?
- 收到  - 好  注意粗口
- Copy that. - Good, swearing?
- 费里曼  - 都嘛是他
- Freeman. - Who could that be?
- 太大声了  - 都嘛是他
- Really loud. - Who could that be?
我在厨房不会被听到的
There's no way you could hear me from back there, man.
你不在外场
Well, you're not out here.
我在外场  我能听到你讲话
I'm out here and I can hear you.
收敛一点好吗？
So let's just bring it down. Yeah?
没礼貌的家伙
You filthy bugger.
好  吧台哪些库存偏低？
Good. Anything been on the bar that we're low on?
君度、气泡、苦啤
Low on cointreau, low on prosecco, low on bitters,
量恐怕腰斩
I'll just give them halves for tonight.
整晚都是
All night.
好  所以量很不够
Okay, so we're low on quite a lot.
还有什么  各位？
Good. Anything else, from you guys?
我们要多推荐素菜
No, just we need to push the veg
要推荐鱼
and we need to push the fish.
- 好  - 好的  主推素菜、鱼
- Sure. - Okay, push veg, push fish.
来合照  上传ＩＧ
We need to take a selfie for the Instagram.
大家一起来
Everybody in.
费里曼  你干嘛  回来
Freeman, what are you doing? Come back.
- 来啦  傻瓜  - 挤一挤  挤一挤
- Come on, you big grinch. - Get squished in.
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
费里曼  又比那个！
Freeman, swearing!
大家动起来
Let's get cracking.
你怎么没说亚历史塔要来？
Why didn't you tell me alistair was coming?
刚才说了
I just told you then.
对  但你没提早跟我讲
Yeah, but why didn't you tell me when you found out?
干嘛介意？
Why would you mind?
- 我觉得准备不够充分
Well, I don't feel like we're prepped properly.
- 为什么不够？你该先准备
Well, why aren't you prepped? You should be prepped.
就不够充分
No, we'll we're not prepped properly.
如果先知道  我就会准备好
If I'd have known, I could have had everything ready.
你本来就该准备好  安迪
You should have everything ready, Andy.
对  但你该先讲
Yeah but you should have told me.
你知道了就该先跟我讲
When you find these things out you should let me know.
- 这是你该做的
That's what you're supposed to do.
- 没时间争这些…
I don't have time to have this-
- 有人要来  你要先讲
- if we have people coming in, you should let me know.
- 我刚才讲了
I just told you then.
他是我前老板  明白吗？
I used to work for the mans, you know what I mean?
我要先准备
So I need to be prepped and ready.
很好  他会喜欢你的风格
Good, then he's gonna like what you're gonna do.
喜欢你你的菜
Yeah. He's gonna like your food.
不用担心
It's fine. Don't worry about it.
- 准备好了？  - 是
- Are you ready? - Yeah.
我要开门了
'Cause I'm opening the doors now.
外面有客人
There's people outside.
这些  帮忙切丁？
Here, can you chop those for us?
好
Yeah.
- 我感觉很差  - 不意外
- I feel like shit, you know. - Well, I'm not surprised.
如果我先退  你可以吗？
You going to be all right if I get off?
什么？
No, what?
如果我先退  你可以吗？
If I get off will you be all right?
安迪  忍住
No, Andy, don't take the piss.
- 我感觉很差  - 不行
- I feel awful. - No, look-
- 我的头快炸了  - 不行
- my heads killing me like. - No, no, no, no, no, no.
你刚开始上工
You've just got here. You just got here.
你不会放我一个人
You're not leaving me in the shit.
好吗？
All right?
不是因为亚历史塔吧？
It isn't about alistair, is it?
不是  我会没事的
No, I'll be all right. I'll be fine.
当然
Yeah, of course.
刀咧  我把刀放哪？
Fucking knives, where have I put my knives yesterday?
我不知道
I don't know.
- 等等我去找  - 好
- We'll get them in a minute. - Okay.
我跟你说  不用担心他
Look, look, you don't have to worry about him.
他是电视上的小丑
He's just some fucking tit off the telly.
你是比他优秀的厨师
You're a better chef then he ever was.
这样很好
And this is good.
那种人来很好  做宣传
Like him coming here, it's good, it's an endorsement.
好吧
Okay, all right.
哇！哇！…
Wait whoa, whoa, whoa.
- 我没事  - 你还好吧？
- Nope, I'm fine. - You okay?
- 没事  - 我跟你说
- Yes. - Okay, look,
如果你觉得…
if you, if you feel a bit like,
需要帮忙尽管讲  好吗？
if you need a bit of help on any just open your mouth, yeah?
完全跟我习惯的不一样
This is completely different to what I'm used to.
- 我知道  - 你动作好快
- I know. - You work so quickly.
- 讲话好快  - 利物浦腔
- You speak so quickly. - It's the scouse.
我听不懂你的口音
Well, I can't understand your accent.
我明白
I know.
你知道的  我是法国人
I, you know me, I'm French,
这些很不一样
but it's very different to what i-
如果你哪里不熟
- I look, if you're having trouble learning,
- 问谁都可以  - 好
- just ask one of us yeah? - Okay.
主动问  好吗？
And just open your mouth, yeah?
问卡莉  卡莉会帮你
Ask Carly. Carly will help you out,
如果我在  我会帮你  好吗？
or if I'm about, I'll help you out, yeah?
好
Okay.
做得怎么样  厨师？
How are you doing there, chef?
温柔爱抚的厨师
Caressing and finessing chef.
不好意思  你说什么？
Sorry, lad, what was that? What did you say?
- 温柔爱抚的厨师  - 做得很好
- Caressing and finessing chef. - Okay, good lad. Good lad.
然后撬开  就是这样
Then we'll see just pop it, that's it.
慢慢转
And turn it nicely.
- 转就对了  - 好
You just turn it?
- 杰克在哪？  - 我不知道
- Where's Jake? - I don't know.
留意他
Keep an eye on him, please, lad.
- 好啦  - 你好
- Yes. - Hello.
儿子
Hey, son.
是
Yeah.
你说什么？
What you came first?
太棒了
Oh that's great, that's fantastic.
非常好  小家伙
Yeah that's superb, well done, lad.
对  没有  对不起  我错过了
Yeah, no, no, I'm sorry I missed it.
好  等下打给你  对不起…
Yeah, I'll call you back in a bit, lad, I'm sorry.
…再见  你去哪了？
Ta'ra. Where have you been?
- 很抱歉我迟到了  - 什么意思  你抱歉？
- I'm really sorry I'm late. - What do you mean you're sorry?
火车慢分
The trains were late. The trains were late.
- 嗨  我吃一口？  - 不行
- Hey, guys, can I have one? - No, no.
就一口  我好饿
Just one. I'm hungry.
你知道你惨了吗？
You know you're in trouble right?
- 罗苹  - 是
- Robin. - Yes.
- 迟到40分钟  - 很抱歉迟到了
- You're forty minutes late. - I'm really sorry I'm late.
你跑去哪？
Where have you been?
- 本来想准时  火车…
I tried to get here on time, the train...
- 我不要听藉口
I don't want to hear your excuses.
- 快去７桌  - 好
Go serve table seven now, quickly.
去就对了
- Okay. - Off you go.
- 试镜怎样？  - 什么试镜？
- How'd the audition go? - What audition?
- 你说她没有试镜
You said she wasn't at an audition.
- 安卓雅…
Andrea and didn't-
晚上好  抱歉耽误了
Evening, guys. So sorry about the delay.
没关系  别担心
Oh, it's okay, don't worry.
我叫罗苹  今晚负责这一桌
I'm Robin, I'm going to be your waitress this evening.
你好  罗苹
Hello, Robin.
今晚想喝点什么？
Can I get you anything to drink.
我要点佐餐酒
Yeah, I'm going to order wine for the table.
好的
Okay.
我要一瓶玛丽堡
Can I get a bottle of the chateau Marie, please?
- 好  - 是红酒？
- Yeah. - Is that red?
对
Yes.
白酒呢？
Bottle of white?
白酒？哪一种？
Bottle of white? Which one?
你知道我爱喝的  亲爱的
You know the one I like, darling.
- 她爱喝贵的  - 没错
- She's got expensive taste. - Rightly so.
一瓶的  哪个最贵？
And a bottle, which is the most expensive?
最底下这个  白苏维浓
It's this one right at the end, the sauvignon blanc.
好  就这个
Oh yeah, we'll take that bottle
白苏维浓
of sauvignon blanc as well please.
好  非常好
Yeah, okay, amazing.
我可以准备水
And I can get some tap water for the table.
不  不要配生水
Uh no, no, not swilling it down with,
毕竟花200镑喝一瓶酒
you know paying 200 pound for a bottle of wine.
有瓶装水吗？
Do you do bottle water?
不好意思
Oh yeah, sorry.
瓶装水？
Bottle of still?
- 是瓶装？  - 一瓶
- Still? - Bottle of still.
很好
Yeah perfect.
瓶装  好的  一般都喝生…
Bottle of still. Yeah I'm used to handing out tap-
我可以喝蔓越莓汁吗？
- can I get cranberry juice?
不要蔓越莓汁  今晚喝酒
No, no, no cranberry juice, we're drinking wine tonight.
你没事的
You'll be fine.
爸  他不能喝啦
Dad, oh my god, he doesn't drink.
他今晚喝酒
He's drinking wine tonight.
好的  两瓶酒
Okay so the two bottles of wine
还有瓶装水
and a bottle of still water.
- 很好  - 好
- Yes, perfect. - Yeah.
好  我去准备
Okay great, I'll go get that for you,
再回来继续点餐
and I'll come back to take your food order.
- 谢谢  - 好
- Thank you. - All right.
抱歉  你叫什么名字？
Sorry, what was your name?
- 罗苹  - 谢谢  罗苹
- Robin. Yeah. - Thanks, Robin.
７桌的酒水
Drinks for table seven.
- 看就知道是他  - 谁？
- Look this is the guy. - What guy?
- 订婚的  - 你们都知道了？
- Engagement guy. - So, you all know?
开会有讲
We had a staff meeting about it.
在这里求婚？女生来了吗？
He's getting engaged here? Is she here?
神队友  帮忙摺餐巾纸
Dream team, fold those napkins,
装一下忙  不要害我
look busy, do not embarrass me.
贝丝攻过来了  快点
Beth is on the war path, come on.
- 你放心  - 谢谢
- You'll be fine. - Thank you.
我有帮你挡一下  抱歉
I did try to cover for you, I'm so so sorry.
我知道  谢谢  你尽力了
I know thank you for doing all you could.
- 顺利吗？  - 还可以
- But how did it go? - It was okay.
很难说  选角导演就…
I think... it's hard to tell, the casting director
没有很确定
was super like, not giving me anything.
我不知道  等消息吧
So, I don't know. We'll see.
什么时候会知道？
When will you find out?
可能下周  可能三个月
Could be next week, or it could be in three months' time.
- 或不可能了  - 别说不可能
- Or it could be never. - Never say never.
- 我该像你一样念大学
Maybe I should just go into the uni like you
找真正的工作  - 乱讲
- and get a real job. - Uni, what's that?
怎么聊起来了？
Girls, I don't know what we're having a chit chat about?
客人等十分钟了
That's been sat there for ten minutes.
安德里亚，去招呼7号桌-
So, Andrea, go and take that table seven.
罗苹  你前面的桌子摆正
Robin, can you go and straighten the tables out in front.
贝丝  客人来了
Beth, there's a customer right there.
- 迪恩  傻傻站在那
Dean, standing there.
都在聊天
There just chatting away.
- 我有叫他们摺餐巾纸  小心
- I told them to fold napkins. - Oh watch it.
对不起
Sorry.
哈罗
Hello.
为您上玛丽堡  还有白苏维浓
So I have your chateau Marie and your sauvignon blanc.
先喝红酒？
Should we start with the red?
罗苹呢？
Where's Robin?
她先负责另一桌
Oh she had to serve a different table.
我是安卓雅
I'm Andrea.
没关系
No worries, yep.
继续
Keep going.
看到一些不想预购的东西
Yeah, see something you wouldn't pre-order it though,
就是那种…
and it's just like that kind of thing that you can't...
对  那种的
Yeah, sort it.
但不只有库存吧？
Yeah but it's not just going to be in stock though, is it?
- 可能吧  - 先生
- It might be. - Sir.
我正在讲话吧？
Yes, in me own time yeah?
怎样？
What?
没事吧？
Nice?
没事
Yeah, it's all right.
没人教你侍酒吗？
Do they not teach you people how to serve wine?
一瓶200磅的红酒
That's a bottle, 200 pound bottle of red wine that.
先让它呼吸  好吗？
Let it breath a little bit, will ya?
白酒需要吗？
White anyone?
你知道吗？
Do you know what?
帮帮忙  放着就好
Just do us a favor, just leave the wine there.
我自己来
I'll sort it out.
好的  需要任何东西请告诉我
Sure, just let me know if you need it anything.
会啦
Yeah, we will.
- 谢谢  - 好的
- Thank you. - There you go.
- 感谢  - 你们俩的酒单？
- Thanks so much. - Wine list for you both?
麻烦你  还有鸡尾酒单
Yes, please, and the cocktail menu.
- 当然  - 谢谢
- Sure. - Thank you.
奈特还好吗？
How's Nate?
他很好  非常好
He's good yeah, yeah, very good.
- 游泳第一名  - 真的？
- He came first in his swimming. - Did he?
- 对  - 他是好孩子
- Yeah. - He's a good lad.
他怎么样  他的反应？
How's he, how's he coping?
- 他很好  - 是哦？
- He's doing all right, yeah. - Yeah?
我有联络凯莉
Oh listen, I've been trying to get a hold of Kelly,
她封锁我还是怎样
I don't know if she's blanking me or what,
我不知道圣诞节送什么给奈特
but I have no idea what to get him for Christmas.
送他一台ＰＳ
Get him a PlayStation game.
- ＰＳ？  - 对
- PlayStation? - Yeah.
我不知道他想要ＰＳ
I didn't know he had a PlayStation.
在凯莉家不准
Oh, at least not at Kelly's house.
在我家可以有一台吧？
But he can have one at my place, can't he?
- 你搬到公寓？  - 对  昨晚搬的
- What you go the flat? - Yeah, I moved in last night.
很好
Good, that is good.
这就是为什么忙到昏头
That's why I was all over the fucking place.
- 好吧  - 你知道我很抱歉
- Well, all right. - You know I'm sorry.
至少你睡觉时
Well, at least you won't be sleeping
不用再睡店里了
on the office floor anymore, yeah?
谢谢你掩护
Thanks for covering.
拜托下次先跟我讲
Just call me next time, please.
- 我明白  - 好吗？
- I know. I know. - Yeah?
这一点我很感激
I really appreciate it.
因为我帮不了  你先讲我才能帮
Cause I can't help you, if you call me I can help you.
你不讲  我帮不了
If you don't call me, I can't help you.
- 我懂  - 主厨？
- I know. I know. - Chef?
- 是？  - 苹果…
- Yeah? - The apple?
是？
Yeah?
希望怎样切？
How do you want it for the salad?
头尾  去头去尾
Top and bottom, chop the top and bottom off.
就是这样  对
That's it. Yeah.
好  然后切片
Okay, and then slice it down.
生蚝够吗？
You got enough oysters there?
不够  我用完了
No, I ran out now.
用完了怎么办？
Okay, so what'd you do when you run out?
是  主厨
Yes, chef.
- 用完了怎么办？  - 继续拿
- What you do when you run out? - Get some more.
用完了怎么办呢？
Sorry, what do you do when you run out?
- 继续拿  主师  - 对  继续拿
- Get some more, chef. - Yeah go on, lad, that's it.
好伙伴
Go on good lad. Good lad.
好  继续切
All right chop it again.
好  然后
Okay and then just...
对  再来
Yep, and again.
你知道怎样切了
And you know what to do know, yeah?
- 法式切丝  - 法式切丝  对
- Julienne okay. - Julienne, there you go.
法式你会的
Your French, you should know that one.
对吧？
Oui?
对  很好
Yeah, yeah, that's good.
再切一颗
Go again.
主厨？
Chef?
小哥哥需要帮忙
The little guy needs some help.
别闹他
Leave him alone,
他做完甜点才开始长毛
he thought he found a pube until he pissed out of it.
你们两个别闹
Hey, you two pack it in.
你  注意袖子  不要沾到
Hey you, sleeves.
怎么了？这是怎样？
What's going on? What's all this?
安迪
Oh, come on, Andy.
怎么会这样？堆这么多？
I mean, why you got all these? What's all these?
我做两个人的工
I'm working for two people here.
你说呢？
What you mean?
你自己看  要我说什么？
Look at the state of it, do you know what I mean?
你说呢？
What, what you mean?
- 杰克还没来
Jakes supposed to be here that's why.
好好好
Okay, okay.
对  我没有三头六臂
Exactly I don't have the power of multiplication.
- 对不起你  - 好好好
- Sadly for you. - Okay all right.
我做得很辛苦  突然就
And I have really tough work here, but suddenly-
好啦  你做得很好
- okay all right, well, you're doing great...
我做得很好  但我需要帮手  你懂的
Yeah, I'm doing great, but I need some help here you know.
好  慢慢洗  可以吗？
All right, all right, just take your time, love, yeah?
慢慢洗
Just take your time.
不用那样吧？
All right there's no need for that is there?
好
Okay.
主厨  这是柠檬馅
Chef, this is the lemon curd
准备放进蛋白酥杯
that we're putting in the meringue.
好
Okay.
怎么样？
What do you think?
- 有点酸  - 调一下
- A bit tart. - You can change that.
你会调  对吧？
You know what you need to do, don't you?
要调一下
Yeah, he needs to find something,
加点别的东西
bring something else into it.
- 谢谢  - 好
- Thank you. - Yeah.
是我没教好
That's mine, that's my fault.
好  拿过来我看一下
All right, bring it here darling, let me have a look.
我再回来试吃
I'll be back in a minute for a taste.
该怎么做？
What you gonna do?
我不知道  还要做饼干
I don't know, but I have biscuits to make too.
你会乱掉
Well, you're gonna get in a right mess
你要先…怎么了！
if you don't start to... what are you doing?
来  先停一下
Come here, please just put it down for a second.
看着我  先不讲这个  好吗？
Okay, look at me we're not going to do this now, okay?
我答应你  我没事的
I promise you, I'm all good.
我懂  之后再讲
Shh, I know but we'll talk about it.
先不讲这个
We're just not going to do it now,
周围太多人
cause there's too many people around.
好的-
Okay.
我们合作  我和你
We'll just need to do it together, just me and you.
好的
Please.
你没事吗？
You gonna be all right just now?
我很好
I'm okay.
跟我一起深呼吸？
Could you do a big breath for me?
一起来  因为我也需要
Let's do it together 'cause I need too as well.
好  继续吧
Okay, good lad, go on then.
我吃一口
Come on then, let me have a taste.
- 谢谢  - 不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
超好吃
That is gorgeous.
真的吗？
Really?
刺激感刚刚好
Ooh, it's just got the right bit of a sharpness.
- 谢谢  - 太完美了
- Thank you. - That is perfect, darling.
- 玛丽亚！  - 你搞什么啦？
- Oh, Maria! - What is wrong with you?
你跑去哪了啦？
Where the fuck you been?
- 蛤？  - 你疯了吗？
- What? - Are you mad?
- 我疯了吗？  - 你迟到两小时
- No, am I mad? - You're two hours late.
你迟到两小时
You're two hours late.
我的闹钟没响  太瞎了
Look, look my alarm didn't go off, and it was madness.
不要鬼扯
No, no, no, no don't come with this shit.
你迟到两小时  都我一个人做
You have been two hours late and I've been doing this alone.
你跑去哪？
Where you been?
她一个人洗
She working on her own here.
我九点到的  迟到半小时
I was has here at nine 30 minutes ago.
乱讲
No, you wasn't lad.
迟到两小时了
It's been two hours ago.
你的手表呢？
Fucking... Where's the watch lad?
时间观念  可怜的女人
Keep the time up the poor woman's
一个人洗
scrapping away here on her own.
苏菲亚放轻松
Sofia relax, relax, Sofia relax please.
你们玩很爽吗？
Are you guys having a great time?
- 玩很爽吗？  - 苏菲亚  我们爱你
- Oh, you are having fun? - Sofia, we love you.
不在乎我怀孕对吧？
You don't fucking care that I'm pregnant right?
- 每个都…  - 放轻松
- You just fucking everybody- - relax, relax.
- 不要这样  - 别碰我
- No, no, no okay. - No, don't even touch me.
安迪  对不起
No, no, no, Andy, sorry.
他来了  你先休息一下
Look, he's here now, you go and take a little break.
先休息一下
Go on take a little break.
- 你搞什么东西
You, do some bloody work.
我想休息  但回来时
I want to take a break, but I don't want to come back
不想看到东西没洗完
and find that those aren't done.
- 快点洗啦  - 快洗
- Okay, do some fucking work. - Start fucking working.
去休息啦
Have a little break, go and have a little break.
我吃一口
Let me taste that.
苏菲亚到底做了什么？
What's Sofia been doing all this time?
快点洗啦
Just get yourself working, man.
真是的
Bloody hell.
怎么样？
What do you think?
我想也是
That's exactly what I wanted to do.
很赞吧？
Isn't it gorgeous?
非常好
That's lovely, yeah.
- 谢谢  主厨  - 他会了  对吧？
- Thank you, chef. - He's got it, hasn't he?
很好  你儿子有天份
That's nice. You've got talent son.
谢谢主厨
Thank you chef.
真的很好
Yeah that's, no, that's really nice there.
你有前途  先在这里做
Yeah, you're going places. But you're staying here.
再吃一口
No, I want one more.
果然再吃一口
I knew he was going to go back in and have another.
- 好吃  - 谢谢
- Beautiful. - Thank you.
你  赶快倒垃圾
Oi you, get them fucking bins done soon, yeah?
动作快  清掉垃圾
Sharpish. Sort the bins out.
倒完跟我讲
Let me know when they're done.
安迪  你跑去哪？
Andy, where have you been?
我在内场帮忙
I was in the back helping them.
有人问菜单
Someone was on the phone asking about the menu,
但我找不到你
and I can't find you.
我在内场调整甜点
I was in the back fixing the desserts.
你不用在内场
I don't need you in the back.
现在满座  万一有人问菜单
Its full in the restaurant if someone brings something up
我要找得到的人
on the menu I need to be able to find you.
你没看到我很忙吗？
Can't you see I'm busy, do you know what I mean?
我们在外场忙
We're busy in the front.
有人问菜单…
Somebody asking about the menu I don't-
我不能同时出现在内外场
- I can't be out here and there at the same time.
对  我是说让我找得到你
Yeah, I saying I need to able to find you here.
我马上回位子  只是帮忙而已
I'll be there in a minute, I was just helping out.
等一下  你有没有遇到你爸？
No come here, did you have a word with your dad?
昨天我请你转告你爸
I asked you to have a word with your dad yesterday
卡莉调薪的事
about Carly? Raising her wages?
我现在没时间讲这个
I don't have time for this now.
现在不适合讲这个
It's not the time to talk about this now.
不好意思  有酒单吗？
Excuse me, is it possible to get the wine menu please?
好  马上来
Yes, I'll get the drinks menu for you now.
谢谢
Thank you.
乔治
Hey, Georgie,
6桌  两杯浓缩咖啡马丁尼
two Espresso martinis for table six.
- 迪恩  你负责什么？  - 什么？
- Dean, what's your job? - Your what?
你负责什么？
What's your job?
我是你的辣主管
I'm your sexy supervisor.
那为什么14桌找我要酒单？
Right, so why is table 14 asking me for a drinks menu?
这不是我的工作
It's not my, it's not my job.
低头  翘屁股  都听你的
Head down, arse up, do what your told.
听到了  我马上做  谢谢
I hear ya, I'm on it, thank you.
嗨  你好吗？
Hi, how are you?
- 我很好  你好吗？  - 很好  谢谢
- I'm all right, how are you? - Good, thank you.
抱歉  我来晚了
Sorry I'm a little late.
别担心  有订位对吧？
Don't worry, have you got a table booked with us?
我男友法兰克…
My boyfriend frank is-
- 你一定是玛丽  - 对  我是玛丽
- you must be Mary. - Yeah, I'm Mary.
你怎么知道？
How did you know?
我们什么都知道
Well, we know everything.
今天还好吗？
How's your day been?
很忙  但今天是周五
It's been long, it's been long, but it's a Friday.
对  可以放松了
Yeah, now you can relax.
- 喝一杯  - 我喜欢你的发带
- Have a drink. - I love your headband.
- 谢谢  - 很好看  闪亮亮的
- Ah, thank you. - Its lovely, nice and sparkly.
周末嘛
You know, weekend.
对  看起来不错  他在那
Yeah it looks good, but here he is.
- 嗨  宝贝  - 你还好吧？
- Oh, hi, babe. - You okay?
我没事  你呢？
I'm okay. How are you?
- 我很好  - 工作还好吗？
I'm okay. Was your work okay.
- 忙  - 先喝点东西？
- Ugh, long. - Can I get you a drink.
- 我想喝古典（鸡尾酒）  - 好的
- I'd love an old fashioned. - All right.
- 两杯  - 两杯古典马上来
- Two. - Two old fashions coming up.
我发了电邮  她会过敏的  有收到吗？
Also, I sent an email about her allergies, did you get it?
有  提醒我以防万一
Yes, but just remind me just in case.
- 我对坚果类过敏  - 坚果类  不吃坚果
- I'm allergic to nuts. - Nuts, so all nuts.
我会交给厨房
Okay, I'll pass that on to the kitchen.
- 谢谢  - 你还好吗？
- Thank you. - You okay?
天啊  今天真的…
Oh, god, I never thought this day...
酒水送去14桌了没？
All right, so has table 14 got their drinks?
我立刻做
Pouring them as we speak.
动作快一点啦  比利  这招没用
Can you just speed it up. No, Billy not helpful, stop.
- 给他一点爱
- Shh. - Give him some love.
安卓雅  这个交给…
Okay, Andrea, can you take that to table,
交给厨房13桌的过敏物
take that to the kitchen for allergy for table 13.
- 好？  - 好的
- Yep, cool. - Gotcha.
还好吧？-
Everything good?
- 真的吗？
Really?
- 晚点跟你讲
Yeah, I'll talk to you about it later.
- 好  - 好
- It's fine. - Okay.
13桌的过敏物
I have a nut allergy for table 13.
贝丝叫我送来
Beth wanted to pass it on.
为什么没进系统？
Why is it not in the system?
我不知道
I... I don't know.
要进系统
It needs to be on the system.
出餐！
All right, service.
贝丝叫我送来
Beth just told me to pass it on.
- 几桌  - 13桌
- For what table. - 13.
13桌不吃坚果
Okay, no nuts on table 13.
- 是  二厨
Oui, chef.
下次记得输进系统
Just put it on the system, next time yeah?
好  我会的
Yeah, I'll do that.
- 靠  - 没事
- Look at this shit. - Okay, okay.
有人又忘了换卷纸
All right, all right, it's just someone's forgotten to change the till roll, again.
进单！螃蟹  炒时蔬
Okay, order in, one crab, one stir.
是
Yep, yep, yep.
另一单  义式炖饭  鸭肉  烧烤
Another followed by one Risotto, one duck, one brill.
- 是  - 是  二厨
- Oui. - Oui, chef.
螃蟹先处理  东尼？
Crack on that crab, Tony, yeah?
- 是  主厨
Yes, chef.
不知道外场在干嘛
They don't know what the fuck they're doing out there.
靠
Ah shit.
你还好吧？
You okay?
不好  安迪  一大堆单
No, look at all these tables, Andy.
好好好  别担心
Okay, okay don't worry.
给我两分钟？
Right, give me two minutes yeah?
不行  安迪  不行啦
No, Andy. No, no Andy, Andy.
给我两分钟  马上回来
Give me two minutes, I'll be right back.
- 我招呼一下  - 安迪  人不够了
- I'm gonna say hello. - Andy, we are going down.
- 给我两分钟  - 安迪  我…
- Just give me two minutes. - Andy, I need you up...
你会没事的
You'll be all right.
帮她一下  费里曼
Help her out Freeman, lad.
鸭肉煎多久了？
How long on the duck?
- 一分  - 一分？
- A minute. - A minute?
对
Yeah.
卡莉  如果她需要你的爱  关怀一下？
Carly, if she needs you love, give her a hand, yeah?
- 安迪  - 你好
- Hey, Andy. - Hello, mate.
感恩  主厨  感恩啊
Namaste, chef, namaste.
- 很高兴见到你  - 很高兴见到你
- Good to see you mate. - Good to see you.
这位是评论家  莎拉·南珍
This is the critic Sara southworth, as you know.
很高兴认识你
Hello, love, really nice to meet you.
Lovely to meet you.
坐下来  简单喝一杯吧？
Come have a quick glass with us, yeah?
很快的
Just a quickie.
我该回厨房了  '狂风暴雪'
I should really get back to the kitchen, we're snowed under
今天嘛  你懂吧？
today, do you know what I mean?
来吧
Just have a quick one.
喝一杯  没事的
You have a glass of wine all right.
- 好的  - 好棒
- Okay. - Its gorgeous.
谢谢
Thank you, thank you very much.
好了
There we go.
不  这杯是你的
No, there's your glass.
谢谢  敬你
Thank you. Cheers, babe.
- 敬你  - 圣诞快乐
- Cheers. - Happy Christmas.
- 圣诞快乐  - 圣诞快乐
- Happy Christmas. - Happy Christmas.
很好
Oh, that's nice.
好酒
That is good.
我不知道你会来
I had no idea you were coming.
临时决定的  你知道吗？
Well, it was a last minute thing, you know?
这个人说他要来
This one mentioned that he was coming,
我一直想来体验这里的圣诞前夕
and I've been wanting to come here pre-Christmas treat.
你不是来工作的吧？
You're not here in a work capacity, are ya?
我认得那种表情
I know that look.
会怕
It's fear, the fear.
没有啦  下班了
No, no, no, off-duty, off-duty.
你想煮什么都好  主厨
Okay. So just cook whatever you want, chef.
早知道你会来  我会先准备
If I'd known you was coming I would have made sure.
我们是好人
Mate, we're the good guys, the good guys.
什么时候订的？（书）
When did you book?
我的书出版… 2月24日
The book is coming in February the 24th.
不是  什么时候订位
No, no, no not when, when did you book?
决定什么时候要来？
When did you book to come here?
不好意思
Pardon me.
两天前  我有打给你  发讯息
Sorry, two days ago, but I phoned you and texted you,
你没回…
and you didn't get back, but...
- 对不起  - 没事
- Sorry. - It's cool, its fine.
我跟你说  我们是来捧场的
But listen, we're here to support you.
对  你懂的
Yes, and you know just-
你不用我给好评  不用担心
you don't need my endorsement so don't worry about that.
好  看一下
Great have a little look at the...
生意这么好  太棒了
Such a buzz in this place, it's great.
没有啦  今晚比较忙
No, you know, its busy tonight. Very busy.
我很忙
I'm busy.
忙着上电视  大小事
Super busy with the TV stuff and everything.
整个忙到昏头
It's gone mental, but I mean.
- 是哦？  - 对  很棒
- Is it? - Yeah, it's been amazing.
我是说节目大热门
I mean the show's rocketing.
对  我看过一集…
Yeah I saw one episode, it was...
你不是唯一看过一集的人
You're not the only one that saw one episode,
七百万人看
there's 7 million people watch it.
代表整季肯定有内涵
You know, full series. Must be doing something right.
对
Yeah no its-
这份菜单  很眼熟
- this menu is... I could recognize all of this stuff.
都是我会做的菜
I mean this is, this is all my dishes.
做成限量餐也不错
I mean, I love the way it's on a bit of paper, but...
鸭肉佐黄豆
There's the duck with the soy.
那是我的菜
Yeah, that was my dish.
- 嗯？  - 那是我的菜
- Huh? - That was my dish.
我有看到加料  你加了红色苦菜
Well, I can see you've added, you've added the red chicory
小调整
so that's different.
他假装第一次看到这份菜单
He's making out like its his first time to see this,
其实在车上用手机先看过
but he was pouring over the menu in the car, on his phone.
你不会看切尔西踢球
Mate, you don't go and see Chelsea
却没先看对战名单吧？
without looking at the team sheet, do you?
不要去主厨餐厅
So you don't go and see a chef's restaurant
却没先看菜单
without having a look at the menu.
却没把菜单撕烂？
Without picking the menu apart.
没有啦  这很棒
No, no, no, no, mate, it's amazing,
你有这份
and you've got this,
你列的都是经典菜
you know you've got all the classics here.
有那个螃蟹…
You've got the crab, which, which-
- 听起来不错
- that sounds nice.
你一定是用我们家的螃蟹
You definitely, definitely added to that crab at ours.
你做的螃蟹很棒
It's amazing what you did to that.
螃蟹先处理过是我的点子  亚哥
Cleaning the crab was my idea though, al.
明白吗？
Do you know what I mean?
这道菜存在一段时间了
Well, it's been around a while that dish.
- 对  是我的点子…  - 两位
- Yeah, but it was my idea... - You two.
跟你一起改良
To change it with you.
明白吗？
Do you know what I mean?
好了啦  我们不是来批评的
Come on mate, we're not here to criticize.
最好不是啦
Yeah, I fucking hope not.
我觉得他有点嫉妒  你懂的
I think he's a bit jealous, but you know.
我好嫉妒
Mate, I am jealous.
我老实说  这里太棒了
I'll tell you the honest truth, this place is amazing,
- 我好嫉妒  - 谢谢
- and I am jealous. - Thank you.
来都来了
Okay, and we're here
来吃你的菜  捧场主厨
to eat your food and support you, chef.
我得回去工作
Nah, I best get back to work.
- 不要那样  - 是吗？
- Stop doing that. - Yeah?
想点什么都好  我会处理
Just please order what you want and I'll take care of it.
谢谢
Thank you, thank you.
很高兴认识你
It's been really lovely to meet you.
很高兴认识你  很荣幸
Oh lovely to meet you, it's our pleasure.
感谢光临
Thank you, it's a pleasure having you here.
- 谢谢  - 待会儿见
- Thank you. - See you in a bit.
谢谢主厨  祝顺利
Thank you chef, good luck.
- 主厨  我们在'热情'吃过这种螃蟹
Chef, "passione" where we had the crab.
对  当然
Yeah 'cause, of course it was,
因为那是我离开你之后服务的餐厅
cause that's where I went to work after I left you.
所以这道菜跟着我
That's why I took it with me.
对不起
Excuse me, excuse me.
她有问题要问你
She's got a question for you.
那是亚历史塔·斯凯？
Is that alistair sky?
对  是他
Yeah, yeah, it is.
- 我就说吧  - 不敢相信
- See, I told ya. - I can't believe it.
祝您有个愉快的夜晚
Have a nice evening.
- 谢谢  - 请慢用
- Thank you. - Enjoy your drinks.
有看过他…
See I seen him...
出餐！
Service.
进单！  炖饭、鸭肉、鲭鱼
Oder up, one Risotto, one duck, one mackerel.
- 是  二厨
- Oui, chef. - I can't fucking believe that.
- 不敢相信
He brought that fucking Sara thingy with him.
- 美食评论家  - 莎拉什么的
- The food critic. - Fucking Sara thingy.
- 莎拉·南珍  - 对
- Sara southworth. - Yes.
- 真的假的？  - 真的
- You're joking. - No, I'm serious.
- 她很低等  - 烂招
- She's the fucking worst. - Fucking dick move.
- 祝你好运  - 我就说吧
- Good luck. - I told you, I told you.
好  我们确认过4桌
Okay look, we're been reviewed on table four.
大家特别注意
I need you to switch on yeah?
4桌吃什么通通记录起来
I need you to soigne everything on table four.
- 是  二厨
- Yes, chef. - Yes, chef.
很好
Great.
如果他想耍花样
Right, okay if he wants to play those games,
那就来呀
we can play those games.
- 好  - 好
- Okay. - All right.
你没事吧？
It is fine. You all right?
没事  做到哪里了
Yeah, let's get going on what we got.
两份羊肉  前菜  2桌
Okay, two lamb, starters gone on table two.
20桌已经上主餐  5桌的正在做
Mains away on table 20. Table fives working.
好
Okay
很好很好
yes, yes, yes, yes.
好
Okay.
- 5桌还要多久？  - 给你
- How long on table five? - Here.
大约90秒
About 90 seconds.
东尼  过来帮忙
Tony, come and give me a push, mate.
来了-
On my way.
- 你可以吗？  - 可以  靠
- How you getting on, bruh? - Good, ah fuck.
东尼  翻面  继续翻面
Get Tony, keep turning, keep turning.
卡蜜儿  配菜还要多久？
Camille, how long on that garnish.
20秒
20 seconds.
- 10秒  有点急
Give me ten, yeah, bit of a rush.
- 继续翻面
Keep turning, keep turning.
很好-
It's good to go.
来了
It's coming. It's coming.
盘子  谢谢
Plate, love, thank you.
继续翻  翻翻翻  谢谢
Keep cooking it. Turn. Turn, turn thank you.
- 请给我鸭酱  - 好
- I need the duck sauce, please. - Okay.
- 可以吗  - 好
- Ready. - Yeah.
- 靠！  - 主厨  没事吧？
- Shit. - Chey, you all right?
没事
Fuck, it's all right, it's all right.
帮我清一下
Clean that up please. Sorry, lad.
- 是  主厨  - 靠
- Yes, chef. - Fucking hell.
我的错
It's me own fault.
- 快帮我重作一份酱  - 主厨！
Okay, can you get me a new sauce
请尽快-
as soon as possible, please.
谈一下
A word.
我说过注意粗口
What did I just say about swearing?
我的手烫到欸
What do you mean? I've just burnt me hand.
我开会有讲
I just said it in the meeting.
特别讲了
Just said it.
- 我烫到手
Yeah, and I've just burned me fucking hand.
- 厨房、整间餐厅都是
Really loud and we're full in the kitchen, and we're full in the restaurant
你叫太大声
your swearing really loudly. I just said bring it down.
哪里大声了？
What do you mean swear loudly?
不然怎样叫？
How fucking else are you supposed to swear?
- 小声点  - 主厨
- Swear quietly. - Chef.
- 主厨  - 干嘛
- Chef. - What?
- 我去倒垃圾？
Is it okay if I take the bins out?
好  去倒垃圾
Yes, yes, yeah, go and do the bins.
对  倒垃圾
Yeah right, the bins.
- 去倒垃圾
Go and get the bins done.
- 快点  小子
Hurry up, lad.
- 你要把它处理好
You need to get it sorted.
嗨  混蛋
Ho ho, motherfucker.
你还好吧？
You all right?
工作怎么样？
How's work?
压力  我压力山大
It's stress. Stressing me.
抱歉  你说什么？
Sorry, what were you saying.
你都没在听
You weren't even listening.
- 有啦  - 你都没在听
- No, no. - You weren't even listening.
你要亨利对吧？
What do you want? Henry wasn't it?
- 对  - 好
- Yeah, yeah. - All right.
我病了
Yeah, I'm sick.
好啦  我会在里面加料
All right, I put a bit of extra in there.
- 你买这个还是？  - 对  帐先记着
- You paying for this one or? - Yeah, no. Tick.
四笔帐了  很随便欸
That's like the fourth one, takes the piss.
没事啦  荷莉  放轻松
It's okay, Holly, relax. It's okay.
今晚你要干嘛？
What you doing tonight?
我要去找盖莉
I'm just gonna go see Kylie, mate.
要开车  因为我有点饿对吧？
Got to drive for a bit, cause I'm a bit hungry, init?
你几点下班？
What time you finish here?
十二点
12.
- 是哦？  - 十二点
- Oh, yeah? - 12, yeah.
到这里  我接你
We'll still be back, so I'll come pick you up.
- 是哦？  - 对
- Yeah? - Yeah, man.
- 明天呢？  - 对  滚啦
- And tomorrow? - Yeah, go and fuck off then.
靠  婊子
- Fuck you, bitch. - You just call me a bitch?
- 你叫我婊子？对  - 蛤？
- Wha? - Yes, you did.
- 什么？  - 下车啦
- What? - Man, get the fuck out my car.
- 靠  - 闭嘴
- Piss off. - Shut up man.
- 关门啦
- Shut up. - Shut the door then.
- 你的烂车
Your car looks like shit.
- 不要踢门啦
Don't kick the door, you prick.
废物
Fucking soft arse.
主厨
Chef, chef.
垃圾倒了
Done your bins.
做得好  谢谢
Good lad, nice one, thank you.
出餐  20桌
Service on table 20.
- 您的餐点  - 谢谢
- Here's your meals. - Thank you.
没问题  还需要什么吗？
No problem, is there anything else we can get for you?
不  这样就好  谢谢
No, I think that's it, thank you.
- 好的  - 好
- Sure. - Yeah.
已经很好了  谢谢
It's been good, thanks.
- 不好意思  小甜心
Excuse me, sweetie pie,
有事讲一下
let's have a little chat with you.
好
Sure.
老实说  南瓜炖饭
To be honest like, pumpkin Risotto,
这种菜单真的不适合我们
this menu's not really for us.
我不懂这些餐点
I don't really understand anything that's on it.
可以给我们牛排和薯条吗？
Could we just get steak and chips please.
很遗憾没有牛排
We don't have any steak unfortunately.
餐点都在菜单上  - 没有牛排？  - 没有
- What we have is on the menu. - You don't have steak?
鞑靼牛？
Steak tartar?
开餐厅要有牛排
You must have steak, you're a restaurant.
- 你有在用ＩＧ吗？  - 有
- Have you got Instagram? - I do.
我有  3  万粉丝
Cause if you have a look I have 30 thousand followers.
对我好  对你们也好
So I think it's good for me, it's good for you,
对生意也好
it's good for the business.
有鞑靼牛  但没有牛排
You have steak tartar, but no steak.
请不要拍到我
Could you not record me, please.
也许我该找经理
Maybe I'll just have a word with your manager.
我去请经理过来
You know what, I'll go and get my manager for you.
受不了女服务生板着脸
I can't stand it when waitresses don't smile.
帮个忙  看一下那个女生
Do me a favor, check that bird right.
她喜欢我的照片…
She liked my photograph -
我知道她的奶很真
- I know her tits are fucking lively right.
嗨帅哥  还好吗？
Hi, gents, how are we?
- 嗨  美女  你好吗？
- Good evening. - Hi, darling, you all right?
- 我很好  谢谢
Good, thank you.
我的同事说你是IG网红
My waitress just said you're Instagram influencers.
- 其实我有在上电视  - 没错
- Well, I actually I was on TV. - Here we go.
- 哪个节目？  - '密前任'
- Oh, what show were you in? - I was on "text my ex."
- 我有看过  - 第三季主角
- I used to watch that. - He came third.
- 第二季  - 天啊
- Second, actually. - Oh my god.
她臭脸  我们只是点牛排和薯条
But she was a bit moody and we just want steak and chips.
我很抱歉  好的  当然可以
Oh, I do apologize yeah, sure we can do that.
- 标记一些照片…  - 那样很棒
- Tag a little photos out... - That would be great.
也许在ＩＧ上关注我们
And maybe follow us on Instagram.
好  没问题
Yeah not a problem.
太好了  你的牛排是？
Great, how would you like your steaks cooked?
- 我要五分熟  - 五分熟  你呢？
- Medium rare for me. - Medium rare, and for you?
五分熟  那你呢？
Medium rare and for you?
我要烤焦  怎么说呢  - 全熟
Just cremated for me please, love, well, well.
- 真的是全熟
Really well done.
为您提供一轮免费饮料？
And can I get you a complimentary round of drinks.
几瓶啤酒
A couple of beers,
也许一瓶红酒搭配牛排
maybe a bottle of red to go with the steak.
拍拍照之类的
Take some pictures, stuff like that.
那样会很棒
Sure, that would be amazing.
马上来  没问题
Guys, coming up, no problem.
你也拿个杯子
Grab yourself a glass as well.
对  一起喝
Yeah, come join us.
柠檬滴给你朋友？
Lemon drop for you pal, yeah?
我是威士忌沙瓦
I'm a whiskey sour, please.
威士忌苏瓦
Whiskey sours.
- 你说什么？  - 威士忌苏瓦
- Wait what did you just say? - A whiskey sours.
- 那是什么口音？  - 格拉斯哥
- No, what accent is that? - Glasgow.
不好意思美女们  威士忌'沙瓦'两杯
I'm sorry, ladies, a whiskey sour times two.
- 太好了  - 他不错
- This is so good. - He's good.
你想要什么？
What about for you, darling, what you want?
通常我会点长岛冰茶
Well, I normally have like a long island ice tea,
不过今天穿这件衣服？
but I just think like in this dress?
这件美到让我想呼呼
That dress to me is screaming a woo-woo.
- 什么意思？  - 欢呼
- A sorry a what? - A whoop-whoop.
相信我  会喜欢的  味道很好
Trust me you'll love that, it's tasty its tasty.
你们今晚要续摊？
Are you guys going out tonight?
- 对  - 其实我是ＤＪ
- Yes. - Wait, listen, I'm a dj.
是哦？
Are you?
兼职餐厅外场
Aye! I mean moonlighting as a waiter obviously.
好
Okay.
达斯顿商城  知道吗？
At the dalston superstore, do you know it?
就在附近
Just right around the corner.
那是同性恋酒吧？
It's the gay bar, right?
- 对  我老公在门口
Yeah, yeah my husband's on the door
如果想来  我可以加名单
I can get yous on the list if yous want to come?
- 好啊  - 你结婚了  真好
- Oh sweet, yes. - You married, great.
- 今晚最爱这一桌
Listen, yous are my favorite table tonight,
免费招待几杯
so I'm gonna get you some shots.
- 好啊
- Yes. - Okay.
野格炸弹  野蛤利口酒？
Jager bombs, Jagermeister do you like that?
野格？
Jager?
野格利口酒调红牛
Jagermeister... its jagermister with red bull.
- 棕色的？  - 对
Oh, like the brown stuff?
天啊  很像咳嗽药水
Oh my gosh, that cough syrup stuff.
不行  我会过敏
Oh no, no, no, I'm allergic.
- 六杯龙舌兰
Six tequilas.
- 好
- Yes. - Love it.
我得回去忙了
Wait, I need to get back to work,
- 因为你们让我心好乱
cause yous will absolutely get me in trouble.
- 留下来啦
No stay.
没有'那道菜'
That's not on the menu.
小手勿动唷  烦欸
Oh, for fuck's sake.
我爱我的工作
I love my job. I love my job. I love my job.
她居然解开我的围裙
She fucking pulled my pinnie!
- 太冒犯了  - 别吵
- Well, that's offensive. - Shut up.
- 很冒犯吗？  - 很冒犯
- Is it offensive? - It is offensive.
比利  来杯咖啡  要浓的
Billy, can I get a coffee please, a really strong one.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 要特调吗？
Do you want something special in there?
- 要
Aye!
低级
Hey, hey, lower man.
对生意好
It would be really great for business.
- 菜单上没有牛排
We don't have steak on the menu.
- 我知道没有  你能做吗？
I know we don't, can you please just do it?
不行  太忙了  不能那样破例
No, look, we are too busy to be going off course like this.
- 忙得要死  - 你就…
- Look how busy we are. - You're not even that...
- 什么事？  - 她要牛排
- What's up? - She wants steak.
我告诉她菜单上没有牛排
I told her we don't have steak on the menu.
如果很忙  为什么你在内场？
If we're busy why you out the back?
又跑去内场？
Why are you out the back again?
- 什么事？  - 要三份牛排
- What's going on? - We need three steaks.
她不听
She's not listening to me.
没有牛排
We haven't got steaks.
- 我跟她说了菜单没有牛排
I keep telling her we don't have steak on the menu.
- 有生肉  那是明天的份
We've got beef roll, but it's for tomorrow.
切三片做牛排  又不难
Just slice three steaks off that, it's not hard.
卡蜜儿帮一下  切土豆
Camille do me a favor love, chop some spuds.
- 土豆？  - 做薯饼
- Spuds. - Let's make some chips, yeah?
- 马铃薯  安迪  - 没事
- Spuds, Andy. - No, it's all right.
- 艾蜜莉  出来一下
Its chips, chips like fritters.
- 炸薯饼类似炸肉饼  - 东尼  去忙你的事
Tony, get back to your own shit, lad.
- 做薯饼  - 居然让步
I do not believe this.
别担心  - 帮我做一点
It's all right don't worry about it.
- 烦欸  安迪
For fucks sake, Andy.
你为什么每次都听她的？
Andy, why do you always give into her, my man?
什么叫'听她的'？
What do you mean give into her?
靠  我自己做
Fuck off, I'll do it myself for fuck's sake.
- 记得要穿  - 好
Don't forget to put on your nabs.
帮我关门
Close that door.
帮我切三片
All right cut me three off that.
- 是  主厨
Yes, chef.
怎么样？
Good?
亚历史塔那桌
Alistair's table.
- 好  - 你想怎么做？
- Okay, um... - What do you want to do?
你做前菜  我做主餐？
Right, you do the starters and I'll do his mains, yeah?
- 好  - 好  做吧
- All right. - Okay. Call it.
两份特餐  两份螃蟹  两份鸭肉
Two covers, two crab, two duck.
- 是  - 是  二厨
- Oui. - Yes, chef.
- 东尼？  - 好
- Okay, Tony? - Yep.
前菜给我看过才能出
I need you to make sure the starters don't go out before I check them, all right?
是  二厨
Yes, chef.
- 东尼？  - 是
- Tony? - Yeah.
东尼  你在干嘛？
Tony, what are you doing?
今天讲几遍了…
How many times have you been told today about this...
杰克应该要处理
Jake is supposed to be clearing this up, chef.
杰克？
What do you mean Jake?
杰克应该先洗好
Jake is supposed to be clearing it up.
我不知道他在哪
I don't know where he is, init?
- 借过  费里曼  - 靠
Oh, for fucks sake. Move, Freeman.
你在说什么？
What is you talking about?
我找你
I'm here fucking looking for you.
你在干嘛？
What the fuck are you doing?
马上出去
Quick get out, get out there now.
烦欸
Fucks sake come on.
卡莉  炒掉啦
Carly, you've got to fire him.
我知道  苏菲亚
Yes, I know, Sofia.
- 用讲的没用
It's not enough just to tell him.
他不听
He doesn't listen.
在打手枪？
Still wanking, yeah?
东尼好幽默
Ah, Tony funny.
- 没事吧？  - 没事吧？
- Are you all right? - Yes, you all right, yeah?
拿去  别打手枪了
Take these and stop wanking.
一边想你妈
Yeah, wanking off your mother.
- 一边想我妈？  - 喔喔喔！
- Wanking off my mom yeah? - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
白痴兄弟
Idiot bro.
你好废  但我爱你
You are useless, but I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
几比几？
Hey, what's the score?
- 2:1  - 2:1
- 2-1. - 2-1?
- 这个好了  - 他怎么还在这里？
- Right, that's good to go. - How is he still working here?
- 什么意思？  - 我抓到他
- What do you mean? - I just caught him out there
用手机看足球
watching fucking football on his phone.
东尼那边一堆餐盘没人洗
Tony is drowning in trays over there.
我会跟他讲
I'll have a word with him.
不行  用讲的不够
No you need to do more than have a word with him.
那我扣他钱
All right, I'll dock his fucking wages.
每次都随便讲讲
Yeah, well, you keep saying that.
二厨  可以吗？
Chef, how's this?
好  看起来不错
Yes. They look brilliant.
做得好  继续保持
Yes, yes, yes, well done, keep that up.
看起来好棒
They look fantastic.
- 谢谢二厨  - 好
- Thank you, chef. - Yeah.
- 二厨？  - 出餐！４桌
- Chef? - Service on table four.
- 二厨？  - 是
- Chef? - Yeah.
７桌说羊肉没熟
Table seven said the lamb is under cooked.
什么？
What?
他们希望煮熟
They want it to be cooked again.
没问题  本来就是粉红的
No that's fine, it's pink, it's supposed to be pink.
我有尽量解释…
I did try and explain that to them...
- 什么事？  - 你解释了？
- What's the problem? - Did you explain it to them?
- 有  我有说  - 什么事？
- I did. I actually did. - What's the problem?
- 几桌？  - ７
- What table? - Seven.
他们没说要全熟
Okay well they didn't ask for it well done.
这是羊肉  本来就这样
That's lamb, darling, that's how it's supposed to be.
是粉红的
It's supposed to be pink.
- 我知道  我有解释
Yeah, I know, I did explain that to them,
- 他们不听
they still didn't listen to me.
- 几桌？  - 7桌
- Okay, what table is it? - Seven.
我去跟他们讲
Let me go and fucking explain it to them.
先放着  先放着
- Whoa whoa whoa whoa. - Leave it, leave it, leave it.
把肉煎到柴掉就对了
Just fry the shit out of it. Grill the arse off it.
应该这样做才对
That's how it's supposed to be cooked.
煎成木炭啦  小声点
Turn it into fucking charcoal, lower your voice.
- 麻烦下次先解释
Explain next time please.
- 好  我会的
Yes, yes, I will.
烦
For fuck's sake.
为什么被退餐？
Why was that plate sent back?
- 没事  处理好了  - 什么问题？
- It's fine, we've sorted it. - Well, what's the problem?
- 没问题  - 有问题
- There is no problem. - Well, what's the problem?
为什么被退？
Why has it been sent back?
我问怎么了
I'm asking what the problem was.
他们说太粉红
They said it was too pink.
客户不满意
Right, so the customer wasn't happy?
那就是问题
That's what the problem was?
不  问题不是这个点
No, no, the problem wasn't that.
你的外场没有先解释…
The problem was your staff isn't explaining...
我的外场有问题  可能吗
So it's my staffs problem. 'Cause if it is that,
客人退餐
they've sent the plate back,
因为不满意
because they're not happy with the food.
问题很简单
It's quite simple.
羊肉本来就是粉红的
The lamb is supposed to be pink.
你知道煎羊肉是粉红的吗？
Do you understand that the lamb is supposed to be pink?
这不是外场的问题
It's not my staff' s issue, it's not about that.
你知道煎羊肉…
Do you understand that the lamb is suppose-
- 粉  红  的  - 我是说客人永远是对的
- I'm saying the customer's always right.
看看-
Look, look, look, look
- 你懂这道菜怎么做吗？
do you know how the dish is supposed to be?
- 两位…
- Girls, girls, girls. - No, no, no.
这道菜怎么做
Do you know how the dish is supposed to be cooked?
你懂吗？
Do you?
其实一直发生退餐
Because what keeps happening, is that plates keep getting sent back
因为你没把外场教好
because you're not fucking training your staff properly.
- 那不是…  - 是
- That's not my, that not- - yes, it is.
我们在这里跟你一起上班
We are working our fucking arses off here and you.
你知道吗  安迪？
You know what, Andy?
我受不了被这种外行骂
I'm sick to the back teeth of your fuckups being blamed on us
看看厨房每个人这么拚
look how hard everyone's working here.
每个人努力替你赚钱
Look how hard everyone is working to earn you money,
但你一直…
but you keep...
你乱掉了啦
You just haven't got a fucking clue.
在厨房忙到死  因为你排订位
We run off our arses here, because you hold the book.
你太蠢了
But you're so fucking stupid
- 甚至不知道自己很蠢
that you don't even know that you've done it do ya?
- 好了啦
Okay.
知道订位超额了吗？
Do you realize that you have overbooked?
- 卡莉  - 不行
- Carly. - No? No?
重点是她改菜单
And on top of that, she's asking us to go off menu,
为网红煎牛排
to cook fucking steak for some bullshit influencers.
永远不会把过敏单输进系统
And never put the allergies on the system,
只能看你写得歪七扭八的字条
so were having to refer to your scrawny handwritten fucking note all night.
知道我们承受多大的压力吗？
Do you know how much pressure we're under?
你知道吗  也许！
You know maybe, maybe, maybe...
也许你花一半的时间学习餐饮管理
Okay maybe, if you spent half as much time learning how to
而不是上社交媒体
run a restaurant instead of whoring your arse
勾引类似廉价的卡戴珊
on social media like a budget fucking Kardashian,
我们就不会这么囧
then we wouldn't be so much in the shit that we are now.
你的口气
You talk to us all,
把我们当成鞋底污垢
like we are the dirt on the bottom of your fucking shoe.
我跟你讲啦  我受够了
Well I'll tell you something, love, I've had enough of it.
我  不  喜  欢  你，他们不喜欢你
I do not fucking like you. They don't like you.
没人喜欢你
Nobody likes you.
这里不值得
And this job is not worth it.
我没拿到足够的薪水处理这些事
I do not get paid enough to deal with this shit.
我没拿到足够的薪水  听到没？
I don't get paid enough, do you hear me?
就算加薪
Even with the wage increase.
你还是要改一下态度
So you better adjust your attitude love.
什么加薪？
What wage increase?
两位  不要现在讲
Girls, girls, come on, not right now.
什么？
What?
先停
Leave it. Leave it. It's okay.
- 什么？  - 先停
- What? - Leave it.
她再这样讲话就滚
She talks to me like that again, she's gone.
- 我跟你说
Okay. Listen, listen, listen.
爸  收到讯息可以回电吗？
Dad, could call me back when you get this please?
我不适合做这行
I don't, I don't think I'm meant to be doing this.
我真的不知道我在干嘛
I don't really know what I'm doing,
这里没人喜欢我
and no one really likes me here.
麻烦你回电
Can you just call me back please?
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
很好  怎么了？
Yeah, fine. Why?
来了两位没订位的
We had two walk-ins at front desk.
- 好  - 我只是想…
- Okay. - I just wanted to get...
让我好好上班
Maybe you could let me do my work.
- 我尽量  - 好
- I'll try. - Okay.
嗨  这瓶招待
Hi, guys, here's the extra bottle.
请问要开吗？
Should I just swap, switch it out.
好  开吧  很好
Yeah switch it out, switch it out that's great.
可以来一点乳酪蛋糕会加的萨塔粉？
Also, could I get like a ramekin dish with some zatar.
- 好的
Oh, yeah, sure absolutely.
已经很好了  只是再加一点
This is so good but it just needs a little,
知道不？-
you know?
- 不用担心  我去拿
Yeah no worries at all. I'll get that now.
- 谢谢  萨塔？
- Thank you. Thank you. - Zatar?
你不能单凭一个晚上就否定一位厨师
I mean, you can't turn off the chef for just, just one night?
我跟你说  这很棒  98%很棒
Hmm listen, this is great, it's 98 percent there.
少了什么？
What's missing?
少  2%
Two percent, two percent.
很幽默
Ah, you're funny.
安迪需要我推他一把
You know Andy always needed me to push him to greatness.
不曾靠他自己实现过
Never, never ever achieved it on his own,
以后会吧
but he will.
我确定他会的  我喜欢这道甜点
I'm sure, I mean I like it.
不必所有东西都加液态氮
Not everything has to have liquid nitrogen, or
碎坚果  你知道吗？
rubble of nuts, or, you know?
对  让我开心一下？
Yeah, humor me okay?
就…
Just...
两盘一样
We have the same thing.
说一下吃到什么？
Just, tell me what I'm tasting?
来
Come on.
非常…朴素
It's unpretentious.
内涵不复杂
It doesn't complicate itself.
好吃  很简单
It's lovely, its simple.
什么？
It's what?
- 简单  - 简单
- It's simple. - Simple.
这是朴实无华的简单食物
So we're talking about unpretentious, simple food
做成限量餐点
and paper menus.
你想怎样？
What are you trying to do here?
你要我给负评还是？
Do you want me to give them a bad review or what?
他是我的朋友
That's my friend. He's my friend.
不用给他负评
Okay I don't want you to give him a bad review.
请诚实面对你吃到的
I just wanted you to be honest about what we're eating.
好  因为我蛮喜欢的
Okay, good, because I quite like it.
评论就像性  有就是有
And reviewing is like sex, you go by what's there,
很难假装
not by what's not there.
你懂的
You know.
你还是吃吧
Just eat your food.
猫王  你离开了厨房
Elvis, you have left the kitchen,
所以我们负责享受就好
so let's just enjoy what is here.
您的萨塔粉
Here is the zatar.
请看
Now watch.
- 太棒了  - 是吧？
- Oh, amazing. - Right?
不要捧他
Don't, don't, don't egg him on.
我不要加啦
You don't have to put it on mine.
看起来…
It looks like, it looks like-
- 你会喝一杯  - 他是什么样的人？
- your gonna be drinking. - What's he like?
迷人  帅  很好
Just really charming and handsome, and nice.
- 他真的很迷人吗？  - 对
- Oh he's really charming? - Yeah. Yeah.
不错
Oh cool, cool.
也许他会载你回家
Maybe he gives you a ride home tonight.
- 也许吧  - 不错
- Yeah maybe. - All right, cool.
- 我真的会问他  - 没问题
- I'll ask him actually. - That's no problem.
- 亚历史塔·斯凯怎么样？
Pst, what's alistair Skye like?
- 在聊他很迷人
I was just saying that he was really charming.
你喜欢他
Oh you fancy him.
比利  你才是她的最爱
Oh, Billy, you're the one she loves though.
真的？不像欸
Oh really? It doesn't seem that way.
- 别说出来
Do not say that.
- 今晚我挺他
It's all right, I've got him tonight.
很尴尬
That's embarrassing.
美国人呢  他们会去吗？
How about the Americans, actually, are they going?
你要的烤焦羊
All right, here's your cremated lamb.
安卓雅  我不是针对你
Andrea, I wasn't having a go at you.
拜托告诉他们
Please, just them just tell them
羊肉不是这样煮的
that's not how it's supposed to be cooked.
我会转达
I'll pass the message on.
先生  您的羊肉
Here's your lamb, sir.
那是什么？
What's that?
您之前那一盘…
It's the lamb that we've-
不  那个啦
- not that. That?
你要的话我可以换
If you want I can take it back.
不用  你的脏指纹别碰我的盘子
No, get your dirty fingerprints of me plate.
厨房那边希望我转达
The kitchen did want me to let you know that,
通常羊肉煮成粉红色
usually lamb should be cooked pink,
为您做到特全熟
but just for you we cooked it extra well done.
我知道
- Yes, I know that. - I hope you enjoy your meal.
希望您会喜欢  有个美好的夜晚
Have a lovely evening, guys.
- 太离谱了NThat's ridiculous-
从头到脚晒伤
Head to toe sunburn.
- 这些不用了吗？  - 好妙
- Are you done with these? - It was fabulous.
- 谢谢  - 我去拿主餐
- Yes, thank you very much. - I'll get your mains, okay.
二厨
Chef.
13桌主餐  没有坚果
Mains away, table 13, no nuts.
- 是  - 是  二厨
- Oui. - Yes, chef.
卡莉  我准备要去７桌
Listen, Carly, I'm just about to speak to table
羊肉的事  但…
seven with the lamb, but...
晚点我们可以喝杯酒谈谈吗？
Could we maybe get a drink and talk later?
好
Sure, all right.
Okay good.
主厨  酱用完了
Chef, we're out of house dressing.
好
Uh, okay just-
你要我用别的取代吗？
- do you want me to just use something else?
等我一下
Uh yeah, yeah, yeah, give me a minute.
Give me a minute.
好  怎么样？
Okay, yeah what's wrong?
我现在要调酱汁
I have to serve with now eh-
你希望我怎么做？
- what do you want me to do? - Is that the-
多做一点
make some more, make some more.
但现在只能用这个
But I have to take these right now.
- 那就用这个  - 好
- Okay, well just use that then. - Okay.
但多做一点  好吗？
But make some more of that though, yeah?
- 好  - 暂时先用这个？
- Yes. - Use that for now yeah?
可以的  吃不出来
That will be all right, no one will know.
- 好  - 多做一点
- Okay. - Just make some more though.
确保多做一点
Make sure you make some more up.
烦欸  烂东西
For fuck's sake, fuck these things.
- 你没事吧？  - 不  我快倒了
- You all right? - No, I'm fucking exhausted.
等一下
Whoa, whoa, whoa hold on.
进单！
Okay, order in,
生蚝  螃蟹  鸭肉  鲭鱼
one oysters, one crab, one duck, one mackerel.
不  等一下
No, no, no, you'll have to hold that.
- 那个拿回来  - 等一下
- Hold on take that back. - Hold on, hold on.
- 进烤箱  - 进吧
- It's gonna go over. - Just leave it, hold it.
出餐  13桌
Service on table 13.
你没事吧？
You all right?
备用锅呢？
Where's the back-up container?
你没事吧？
You all right?
没事  我处理
It's all right, I'll fix it.
开喝  同事们
All right, drink up lovely people.
好的  大家喝一杯
Okay guys here we go.
她去哪？
Where'd she go?
- 她离开我  - 蛤？
- She left me. - What?
上洗手间
Nah, the toilet.
- 时候到了打暗号
Give me the signal when it happens, yeah?
- 别担心
Don't you worry, mate.
- 安安  - 你好
- Hello, my lovely. - Hello.
- 你好吗？  - 我很好
- How are you? - I'm great.
你今晚外出吗？-
Do you want to go out tonight?
你不想和阿利斯泰尔·斯凯出去吗？-
You don't want to go out with alistair Skye?
不  我会跟你一起出去
No, I guess I'll go out with you.
- 我家？  - 不行唷
- My place? - Uh, excuse me, no.
我们今晚要出去  你要来吗？
We're gonna go out tonight. Do you want to come with us?
我在夜店做ＤＪ
Yous going out? I'm djing at the club.
哇靠ＤＪ  你在哪一家？
Fuck off you're djing at the club, which one?
商城那一家
- I know where were going to go. - The superstore.
- 好  - 好  我们走吧
- Yes. - Yes, let's go.
- 美国人会来吗？
Are the Americans coming by any chance?
- 会  美国人会来
Yes, the fucking Americans are coming.
跳舞！
- Is it? - Americans and-
- 美国人来是一个笑话…  - 13桌主餐吃完了
- this is a joke.. 13s mains are gone?
等等-
Hold on, hold on.
- 对  13桌出完
Yeah, yeah, 13 is gone.
- 感谢
Cheers, pal, thank you.
好的
All right.
- 还好吗？  - 没事
- You good? - Yeah. Yeah.
酱汁还要多久
How long on the sauce?
酱汁还要多久  安迪？
How long on the sauce, Andy?
熟度到了  该出了
This can't go any longer, its gotta go.
好
Okay, all right all right.
开始摆盘
Let's get this going, all right.
- 好  - 好
- Yeah. - Yep.
- 好
Okay.
你少放一块
Okay you missed a piece there, yeah?
对
Yeah, yep.
这里两块
Here's two.
- 清一下  - 盘子要擦
- Let's clean that. - Wipe that plate off.
好
Yep, all right, all right.
- 好了？  - 好
- Yeah? Yeah? - All right.
- 可以？  - 好了  满意吗？
- Yeah, you've got it? - Yeah, you happy?
好
Okay.
不  我来端
No, no, I'll do it. I'll take it.
- 好  - 我端过去
- All right. - I'll take them.
- ４桌  对吧？  - 对
- Away on table four, yeah? - Yeah, yeah, got it.
- 好了？  - 对
- Good? Good? - All right, yeah.
好
Okay.
- 卡蜜儿  看一下薯饼
Camille, check them chips, love.
- 是  主厨
Oui, chef.
很好  谢谢
Great, thanks man.
太棒了  太棒了
Amazing. Amazing.
- 她去哪？
Where's she gone?
她去打电话
She's just making a call.
好吃  主厨  真的好吃
That's good, chef, that's really good.
酱汁…  酱汁没有很足
Sauce is, something not deep about the sauce.
时间不够
Just didn't have enough time.
Didn't have enough time.
不错了  只差一丁丁
It's good though, it's just millimeters.
早知道你会带她来就好了
I wish I would have known you was bringing her.
为什么？
Why?
我们可以提早准备
Well, then we could have got ready.
明白吗？
Do you know what I mean?
你有准备好  这很棒
You are ready. This is great.
有点过分  带她一起来？
Bit strong isn't it, bringing her along?
我们是好人  来捧场
We are the good guys, we're here for you.
你老婆知道她跟你一起？
Does your missus know she's out with ya?
我没有要开玩笑
You know mate, I'm not being funny or nothing.
这是怎样？
What's this all about?
是你不回我电话
Mate, you haven't returned
六周不回我电话
a call to me in six fucking weeks, all right.
我没必要亲自跑来
I shouldn't have to come down here, all right,
搞清楚怎么回事
to find out how we're doing?
知道我在说什么吗？
You understand what I'm saying?
六周不回
Six fucking weeks.
你想知道到底是怎样？
You know, you want to know what this is about?
是吧？
Right?
因为你从我这里
This is about you taking
拿走200,000镑
200 thousand fucking pounds off me...
- 不好意思？  - 对不起
- Excuse me? - Sorry.
200,000镑
200 thousand.
可以合照吗？
Could we just have a quick picture.
今晚好友聚会  可以吗？
Bit of a fanboy moment, is that all right?
因为你人间蒸发
Cause you disappeared off the face of the fucking earth.
来吧  很快
Yeah, no come on, come on quick lads, lads.
可以吗？
You take it all right?
给你  谢谢
Here you go, thank you for this.
太好了  感谢
Cheers, thanks you for this.
多拍两三张好吗？
Can you get two or three mate?
主厨（人间蒸发了）
Hey, chef, disappear off the fucking earth.
嘿-
Hey.
不错唷
Nice one, mate.
好
All right, lads.
谢谢你
Thank you.
可以来点苏打水吗？
Could we get some sparkling water for the table, please?
他是主厨  去问服务生
He's the head chef, mate, ask one of the girls.
问其中一位女生
Ask one of the girls.
- 他都来了  - 问其中一位女生
- He's already here. - Just ask one of the girls.
对不起  主厨
Sorry about that, sorry, chef.
- 需要什么吗？
Can I get you anything else at all?
我只剩几个月的时间  真的
Mate, I'm months away, really.
电视节目那些东西
Okay all the TV and the blah, blah, blah.
我距离破产只剩几个月  真的
I'm months away from going under, I mean it.
我需要那笔钱
All right I need, I need that money.
我不能给你  亚哥
I can't give it to you, al.
我没钱
I haven't got it.
I don't have it, mate.
我本来想慢慢还
I was trying to pay you back bit by bit.
那样对我没用
Well, that's no fucking use to me anymore, mate.
我需要那笔钱
I need it.
你知道如果我倒了
Do you understand how many people are going to go out of
会有多少人失业吗？
work if I go under?
我需要你帮我
I need you to help me, mate.
你还钱
I need you to give me the money.
我现在没钱
Well, I haven't got it.
没有钱没办法还
I can't give you what I haven't got.
你知道你有什么吗？
You know what you do have?
你有这个地方
You've go this place.
这个地方很值钱
This place is fucking gold, okay.
让这里完美  一起做
Perfect what we're doing here, but do it together.
我们重新合作
We could back... Back together.
我已经有合作伙伴
Listen, I've already got a partner in it.
不管你有什么伙伴  加我  好吗？
Mate, whatever partner you've got, you let me in, okay?
- 这是我的
This is mine.
- 这地方很好
This place it great okay, but it doesn't make
但不赚钱  因为你没有商业头脑
a fucking penny cause you don't have a business mind.
我有  你做你该做的
I do. You just do, you do what you do in there,
我做我该做的  我们分润
and let me do what I do out here.
七三分
We split it 70/30.
- 我不行  - 为什么？
- I can't do that. - Why?
我还有其他伙伴
I've got other partners.
你拿三成随便你分
You've got 30 percent to split anyway you fucking like.
三成很多了  好吗？
All right, 30 percent of a lot is a lot, okay?
接受吧
Agree to this,
不仅莎拉会做好评
and it won't just be Sara who'll do good reviews.
你还会得到口碑
You'll get reviews from everyone in town.
拜托  我需要这样做
Please, I need this.
宝贝
Hey babes.
不好意思  打电话给我小孩
Hi, sorry, sorry, just on the phone with my kids.
我那些前任  就…
Who are at my exes, it's just a...
看起来很棒  主厨
Well, this looks great, chef.
谢谢
Thank you.
好棒
Well! Beautiful!
还好吗  我错过什么？
How are you, what have I missed?
没事  聊聊过去
Nothing. We're just catching up.
对了  这个很棒
This is great by the way.
你会爱吃的
You wait to you taste this.
煮得很漂亮
It's beautifully cooked.
- 谢谢  - 哪一家的？
- Thank you. - Where's it from?
粉红  我们从史密斯那里买鸭肉
We sourced the duck from smiths.
世界最棒的肉商
Best meat supplier in the world.
我们餐厅指定使用
We always used them in our restaurant.
好吃
No, it's beautiful.
做得好  我不知道你如何兼顾两边
Well done, I mean I don't know how you juggle both this,
工作与生活（双关）
and life and...
- 你有小孩吗？  - 有
- Have you got kids? - Yeah.
有？几岁？几个？
Yeah? How old? How many?
- 我有一个儿子  - 是
- I've got a little boy. - Yeah.
不好意思  奈森
Nathan.
不错  名字不错
That's nice, that's a good name.
我有两个  都是女生
Me, I've got two, but both girls and,
我刚才打电话说明在外面吃饭
you know I was just on the phone trying to explain why
破例一晚
I have to be out for just one night.
我很高兴来这里  但你总觉得
I'm glad I'm here, but you just always feel like
你…
you're a...
想表达歉意  总之
You have to apologize for... anyway.
你要缓一缓就对了
Just needed a break, and uh-
怎么可能不会倒？
how do you do not burn out?
- 烦  - 这…
- Fuck's sake. - It's a...
你知道怎样不会倒吗？
You know, the way to not burn out?
知道餐厅的成功秘诀吗？
You know the way to achieve a successful restaurant?
自信心和好团队  对吧主厨？
Is confidence and a great team, right, chef?
主厨可以很普通
You can have a very mediocre chef, surrounded by
配合团队不错  餐厅就成功了
a great team and you've got a successful restaurant.
或者主厨超烂  配合团队超强
Or you can have a shit chef surrounded by a great team.
我觉得男人放轻松  对你们两个都好
Well, good for you two. I think men have an easier time of it.
你知道做错什么吗？
You know what your fault is?
你人生唯一的错误
The trouble is you made one mistake in your life,
就是嫁给那个人
and that was marrying the man you married.
我不算嫁给一个  自私的、自溺的
Well, I didn't exactly think I was marrying a selfish,
- 自命不凡的自恋狂
self-obsessed, pretentious, narcissist.
- 嫁给自恋狂？
You married a narcissist?
谁会爱上、嫁给自恋者？
Now who falls in love and marries a narcissist?
对不起  我接个电话
Excuse me I'm sorry, I've just got to take this call.
抱歉
Okay sorry.
哈罗  儿子
Hello. Hello, son.
对  不是  我很抱歉
Yeah, yeah no, I'm really sorry.
对不起  我说会打给你
I said I try and call you back.
- 救命！她卡到了
Can somebody help me? She's having a stroke.
我要去忙了  好吗？
All right, listen, I've got to go, okay?
等等再打给你
I'll phone you back in a minute.
- 我保证  - 先扶你起来
- I promise you. - Let's get you up.
她吃到会过敏的东西？
Is she allergic to anything?
出去透透气
Let's get you outside, sweetheart.
- 怎么了？  - 她突然窒息
- What's happened? - She's having a shock.
- 你想出去吗？  - 服务人员陪她出去
- Do you want to come with me? - The staff are away, yeah.
她还好吗？
Okay is she okay?
我在叫救护车
I'm just on the phone to the ambulance.
- 食物的关系吗  安迪？  - 我不知道…
- Was that the food, Andy? - I have no idea, I...
我不知道
I don't know.
- 主厨  她没事吧？  - 应该没事吧
- Chef, she all right? - Yeah, I think so, yeah.
应该没事  我不知道
Yeah, she's all right. I have no idea.
- 外场怎么了？
What is going on out there? There's all this-
我不知道  她…
- I have no idea. I don't know, she...
- 发生什么事？
What happened?
我不知道
I have no idea. I don't know.
我不知道怎么了
I don't understand what's going on out there.
我不知道
I don't know. I... just give me a minute.
给我一点时间
Give me a minute.
根本就没写
It's not there, at all. Fuck!
我知道  到底怎么了
I know, I don't really understand what happened.
她还好吗？
Is she okay?
应该没事  我还在看
I think so, yeah. I'm just checking up now.
- 她还好吗？  - 她一定很难受
- She okay? - She must be so hurt.
你只负责做菜
Excuse me, excuse me, you had one job.
就一件事
One fucking job.
却把我女友害成这样
Look what you've done to my girlfriend.
- 我们真的很抱歉  - 乱七八糟
- No, we're really sorry. - No, this is a shambles.
都被你毁了
You ruined everything.
冷静一下
Calm down. Calm down.
谁有毛毯或外套之类的吗？
Do you have a like a blanket or a jacket or something,
我的放在里面
because my jumper's in there.
我觉得她是过敏反应
I think she's having an allergic reaction.
- 没人告诉我  - 她对坚果过敏
- Nobody told me this. - She's allergic to nuts.
- 怎么没输进系统？
How did it not get in the system?
- 我不知道
I don't know.
- 怎么会这样
Has nobody put it in the system?
-对
Yeah.
等等跟你讲
I'll let you know in a sec what's going on.
- 发生什么事？
What happened?
我有外套
I've got the jacket.
要顺着一个方向…
You have to go around the one way-
外套给我
- give it to me.
披在她身上
Give it, put it around her.
还需要什么吗？
Is there anything else you want me to get for you?
不用  走走走
No, there's nothing, go, go, go.
- 我先回…
- Fucking hell. - I'm just going to-
- 安卓雅  我知道
- Andrea, I know, I just want to say you've done
今晚表现很好  谢谢你
really well tonight and so thank you.
今晚很辛苦
It's been a really tough night.
也许我们周末喝点东西之类的？
Maybe we could get a drink or something in the week?
好
That would be nice.
我要带救护车
I'm just going to go flag the ambulance down.
确认一下迪恩没事
Do want to go check that Dean's okay?
我听到救护车的声音  我去带路
I think I can hear them, I'm just going to flag them down.
车就在外面
They're literally seconds away.
用鼻子吸  嘴巴吐气
Breathe in your nose, through your mouth.
鼻子吸  嘴巴吐气
In your nose, out through your mouth.
想一下芬兰
Think of Finland, yeah?
我们到芬兰看星星…
When we go to Finland and gonna look at the stars-
- 他们问的我不会讲  细节
- they're asking for things I don't know, detail-
- 好
- okay, okay. - Its fine, its fine.
- 喂？她叫玛丽·格拉斯特
Yeah, her name's Mary glaster.
继续呼吸
Just keep breathing, okay?
- 怎么会这样啦？
How the fucking hell did that happen?
- 我不知道
I have no idea, I don't know.
好吧  现在我也帮不上忙
Ah okay there is nothing I can do now.
你要专心一点
Mate, mate, mate, you've got to concentrate, yeah.
餐点怎么会有过敏物？
How did that plate get contaminated?
我不知道…
I have no idea. I don't, I don't know.
- 谁做的？  - 应该是…
- Who cooked the meal? - It would have been-
- 谁是二厨？
- who's the sous chef?
应该是费里曼  卡莉有责任
No, it would've been Freeman, Carly would have sent it out.
我跟你说  卡莉要扛这个责任
Listen, Carly has got to take the bullet for this, okay,
否则变成你扛
cause otherwise you will, okay?
这是你的餐厅  我的钱  懂吗？
This is your restaurant, this is my money, okay?
- 你要把卡莉推出来  - 我不行
- You have to put Carly on it. - I'm not doing that.
- 为什么？  - 这不是卡莉的错
- Why? - It's not Carly's fault.
谁的错不重要
It doesn't matter whose fault it is.
错误与客人随着救护车远离
Fault leaves with her in this ambulance, all right.
你必须这样做
You got to do this.
做正确的决定
You've got to make the right decision.
必须立刻决定
You've got to make it right now.
你必须这样做  好吗？
You've got to do it, okay?
别无选择了啦
You've got no fucking choice.
谢谢你们  她就在这
Thank you, guys, she's just over here.
- 麻烦快一点  - 你好吗？
- Quick as you can please. - Hi, how are you?
- 嗨  - 嗨  玛丽
- Hi, okay. - Hi, Mary.
我叫萝拉  她是凯萨琳
My name's Lola, this is Catherine.
我们会帮你  好吗？
We're gonna help you, okay?
说一下你吃了什么东西？
Would you be able to tell me what it is that you've eaten?
- 她有打肾上腺素？
Has she got an epipen?
- 有  什么时候打的？
- Yes she does. - Has she used it? When?
大概…50分钟前
Yeah about five, five, ten minutes ago.
别担心
- I don't know. - Not to worry.
她会没事吗？
Is she going to be all right?
玛丽  我现在替你量脉搏
I'm just going to take your pulse, Mary.
慢慢呼吸就好
Breathe really slow for me.
加油  宝贝  我在你身边
Come on, babe, I'm with you. I'm with you.
没事的
It's all right.
很好  慢慢来
Nice and really nice and slow.
慢慢深呼吸
Really slow deep breathes.
脉搏快  但很弱
Okay, pulse is fast but weak.
帮她打肾上腺素
Okay, I'm just gonna give her an epipen.
凯萨琳帮你打肾上腺素
Catherine's just gonna give you another epipen all right?
轻轻刺一下  玛丽？
Just a short, sharp prick okay, Mary?
- 很好  - 你做得很好
- Well done. - You're doing really well.
- 她还好吗？  - 她会没事的
- Is she okay? - She's gonna be fine.
送她回去？
All right, should we get in the back?
好  我们送她上救护车
Okay, we're just gonna pop her in the ambulance.
先扶你起来
Okay I'm just going to stand you up
坐到轮椅上
and get you into the chair,
然后送你上救护车  好吗？
and then put you into the ambulance, okay?
- 谢谢  - 就是这样  谢谢
- Thank you. - That's it, thank you.
- 做得好  玛丽
- There we go. - Well done, Mary.
- 别怕  我在
- Well done. - It's okay, I've got you.
帮你戴好
Put that back on for you.
好
That's it.
- 做得好  - 戴好
- Well done. - Keep with it.
慢慢呼吸
Breathe in nice and slow for me.
你有开车吗？
- Did you drive? - Can I come with you?
- 我可以跟去吗？  - 可以
Yeah.
你做得很好
You're doing really well, okay?
做得好  你们做得很好
Well done, you guys, well done you.
感谢
Thank you.
嘿  对不起……
Hey, I'm sorry for...
我很抱歉  真的很抱歉
No, I'm so sorry. I'm really sorry.
我…
Just...
不要讲话  他没做错什么
Say nothing, he's done nothing wrong.
别道歉了
Stop apologizing.
交给我的公关公司处理
Let my PR company take care of this.
交给我
Alright, you leave it to me.
好吗？
All right?
我不能那样做
I can't, I can't do that.
我不能牺牲卡莉
I can't get rid of Carly.
听我说  这不是建议
Listen to me. This is no request, all right?
这是200,000的订单
This is a 200 thousand fucking pound order.
做对决定  你完了我也完了
You do the right thing, or you go under and so do I.
靠
Fuck.
如果你可以删掉  我会很开心
I'd be great if you could delete it.
你之前说要上传
You said that you wanted.
只是希望你能删掉…
I'm just asking you to delete it...
- 贝丝  请来厨房  - 好
- Beck, back kitchen, please. - Yeah, sure.
主厨？
Chef, chef, chef?
- 是  - 很好
- Yeah. - Great.
她会没事吧？
Is she going to be okay?
- 她会没事的  - 她还好吗  主厨？
- Yeah, she's gonna be fine. - Is she alright, chef?
对  她没事
Yeah, yeah, she's okay.
去厨房  东尼
Back kitchen now, tone.
现在去厨房
Back kitchen now.
去厨房  都去厨房
Back kitchen. Back kitchen.
好的  那是几桌？
Okay, so what table was it?
13桌
13.
13 okay.
点了什么餐？
What did he order?
他们吃了鲑鱼和螃蟹
They had the salmon and the crab.
两杯古典鸡尾酒
Two old fashioneds.
主餐是鲭鱼
And the had two mackerel for main.
好  所以
Okay, okay, so...
主餐没问题
So the main was okay.
对  我们有检查
Yeah, we've been through it,
这些餐点没有坚果类
there was no nuts in any of those dishes.
确定的
We called it.
然后出餐？
Okay, and you sent them out?
对  那些餐点没有坚果类
Yeah, yeah, and there was no nuts. There was no nuts in that dish.
- 刚才说主餐是什么？
Okay what was the main again?
- 鲭鱼搭配…  你知道改了
It's mackerel with the... you know we changed it,
库存不够
because of the order.
改成苹果沙拉佐辣根酱
So we changed it to apple salad and the horseradish dressing.
我的部分没有过敏原
There were no allergens in my section.
那就没事  都没事
Okay, so we're good then, so we're all good.
不对  另一盘
Um, no, the other plate
不是用辣根酱
did not have horseradish dressing.
是什么酱？
So what did it have on it then?
另一盘吗？
The other one?
我有问你  你知道的  酱用完了
I asked you, you know, we ran out of it.
我请你多做一点
And I told you to make some more.
不是  你叫我做另一盘
No, but for the other plate you asked me-
我请你多做一点
- yeah, but I told you to make some more.
可是另一盘沙拉
Yes, but for the other plate
你叫我用别种酱
you asked me to use the other one.
但不要紧吧？
Okay, so that's all right though, isn't it?
是
Yes. Yes.
- 酱包含什么？
What's in it?
柠檬汁、味噌、米酒醋
Lemon juice, miso paste, rice wine vinegar,
'核桃油'、细香葱
walnut oil, and chives.
- 核桃油  - …亲爱的
Ohhhh... darling.
没事没事
Oh, it's all right, love.
没事  不是你的错
It's all right, it's not your fault.
- 好  - 她上了救护车
- Okay. - She's in the ambulance.
她没有…并没有…
She's not, I mean it's not-
- 我不觉得…  - …很严重
I don't think it's that... That massive of an issue.
- 你真的很笨
You really are fucking stupid aren't you?
- 我说真的  - 好了啦
- All right, man, come on. - No, seriously.
你真的很笨
You really are fucking stupid.
什么叫'没有很严重'？
What you mean it's not much of an issue?
什么叫'没有很严重'
No, what do you mean it's not much of an issue,
- 外面有个女生很可能会…
cause there's a girl out there that's probably gonna fucking...
- 冷静点  不！东尼
- Chill, chill. Chill. - No, no Tony.
有个女生可能会死
There's a girl out there that's probably gonna die.
她都哭了
She's crying her eyes out,
知道是谁的错吗？
but actually you know who's fucking fault this it?
老实说啦
Let's be really honest about it.
你不敢讲  卡莉
You're not going to say it, Carly,
我来讲
so I'm gonna fucking say it.
安迪  你的错
Andy this is your fucking fault, my man.
费里曼  不不不
Freeman. No, no, no, no.
你不准时
Cause you don't turn up in time.
没看库存  没有准备
You don't do the orders. You don't do the prep.
你根本就不关心我们
You don't give a fuck about us.
来到店里全身酒气
You fucking come in stinking of booze.
你…
You're a fucking...
住手！
Stop it.
每个人都要冷静一下
Everybody needs to calm down.
带他出去！带出去！
Get him out of here. Go on out from here.
- 去外场  - 冷静点  兄弟
- Go, go, out front. - Chill, bro.
我们还有客人
We've still got tables.
去啊
Go on.
卡莉  是我的错
Carly, it was my fault.
我叫她用另一种  是我的错
I told her to use the other one, it was my fault.
- 好吧  - 我完了  卡莉
- All right. - I'm fucked, Carly.
好好好
All right, all right, okay, come on, come on, come on.
你保持冷静好吗？
You just need to stay calm all right. Yeah?
深呼吸
Take a deep breathe, just take a deep breath.
我该怎么办？
What am I, what am I gonna do?
我们会熬过去的  好吗？
We'll get through it, all right?
- 但我做错了  - 好好好
- It was my fault, though. - Yeah, okay, okay, okay,
你要一步一步来
but you need to take it one step at a time.
好
Okay.
好吗？
All right? Yeah?
- 主厨  没事吧？  - 不行
- Chef, we all good? - No, no, no, no, no.
滚出去！你滚出去！
Fuck off you, get out, fucking get out right.
离开我的厨房！
Get out of my kitchen.
- 疯子！
Fucking lunatic!
- 你干嘛？  - 卡莉  是他
- What are you doing? - Carly, Carly he wanted me
他叫我牺牲你  卡莉
to throw you under the bus, Carly.
- 你在说什么？  - 我说真的
- What are you talking about? - Honest to god,
他叫我牺牲你  扛责任
he told me to fuckin' let you take the blame for this.
那混蛋
That fucking twat.
我不扛这个责任  不是我的错
I can't take the blame for this, it's not my gaff.
- 我不要扛责任  - 我知道  是我的错
- I can't take the blame. - I know, it was my fault.
这样说不通  安迪  没道理啊
So that makes no sense, Andy. It makes no fucking sense.
卡莉你不懂  我有麻烦
Carly you don't understand, I'm in the shit.
别说我不懂
Don't tell me I don't understand.
我不懂吗？
I don't understand?
我天天都在掩护你  安迪
I'm here covering you arse every fucking single day, Andy.
我再也受不了
I can't fucking take it anymore.
卡莉
Oh Carly.
别说了  好吧？
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, right?
我…
I just fucking...
- 卡莉  对不起  - 不
- Carly, I'm sorry. - No.
我听过太多次了  安迪
I've heard it a lot, Andy.
听过太多次
I've heard it a lot.
不是…
This wasn't, don't do-
- 卡莉  我很抱歉…
- Carly, I'm so sorry...
别说了
Stop it. Stop it. Stop it.
我得走了
I have to go. I have to go.
卡莉  别这样
Hey, Carly, don't.
我必须换工作  安迪
I have to take that other job, Andy.
不能这样下去
I can't do this.
好吗？
Yeah?
拜托不要那样
Don't, please.
- 好
Okay.
你懂吗？明白吗？
Yeah you get it? Yeah, you understand?
对  我明白
Yeah, okay, I get it.
拜托你
Please, please, please, please, please, please.
- 好  你是对的  - 是吗？
- Okay, you know, you're right. - Yeah?
- 你说得对  - 是吗？
- You're right yes. - Yeah?
- 你可以吗？  - 可以
- You gonna be all right? - Yeah.
我要回去忙
I need to get back out there.
好
Okay.
对不起  安迪
Sorry, Andy.
没事  我…
It's all right I just-
没事没事
- it's all right, it's all right, it's all right.
我明白了  给我几分钟时间
I get it, just give me a couple minutes here.
对不起  卡莉  抱歉
I'm sorry, Carly. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
哈罗
Hello.
我知道  我很抱歉
I know I know, I'm really sorry.
我有  我打给他  但…
I did, I tried to phone him, but, um...
我打了  我打给他  但都过去了
I did, I tried to phone him just everything has gone
工作很烦  就是这样  但我有打给他
to shit at work, that's all, but I tried to phone him.
你意思是？没有  我当然爱他
What do you mean? No, of course, I love him.
什么？
What's that?
告诉他我爱他
Tell him I love him.
告诉他  让他知道我爱他
No, tell him he should know that I love him.
我有在做
I am showing it.
没有  我没有
I haven't, no, I haven't.
好
Okay.
不  我没吸
No, I haven't been sniffing.
对  我有做
Yeah, yeah, I did.
对  我做了
Yeah I did.
不  我不知道该怎么办  我想戒
No, I don't know what to do, I just want to stop.
说真的  我想戒
I do honestly, I want to stop.
我想戒  真的很想戒
I want to stop. I really want to stop.
那好吧  不  好吧…
Okay then, yeah no, okay, well...
有必要的话我会去中心
I'll go to rehab if I have to.
对
Yeah.
好
Okay. Okay.
没有  我答应过我会做到
No, it's not, I promise you I'll do it.
好  我明天打给你
Okay, yeah, I'll phone you tomorrow.
好
Okay. Okay.
好  我会的
Okay, I will.
好  我会的  对
Yeah I will. Yeah.
对  我会的
Yeah I will, yeah.
好
Okay.
告诉他我也爱他
Tell him I love him as well.
请告诉他
Please tell him.
好
Okay.
好  再见
All right. Ta'ra. Ta'ra. Ta'ra.
靠
Oh fuck.
安迪  醒醒  安迪！
Andy, wake up, Andy, Andy!
主厨！
Chef. Chef. Chef!
- 主厨！  - 快来帮忙
- Chef! - Can someone help?
主厨！
Chef!
叫救护车！
Somebody call an ambulance!
沸点
（最后有一张照片）